ok so let me dive into some administrator
확인 그래서 내가 어떤 관리자에 뛰어 보자
went first so I can recall that assignment one is due next Wednesday
나는 그 과제를 호출 할 수 있도록 먼저 가서 한 다음 주 수요일 때문이다
yeah but hundred and fifty hours left and I use ours because there's a more
그래하지만 백 오십 시간 왼쪽보다 거기 때문에 우리를 사용하는
common sense of doom and remember that third of those hours he'll be
일반적인 운명의 감각과 그가있을거야 그 시간의 세 번째 기억
unconscious so you don't have that much time it's really running out and you
의식이 그래서 당신은 많은 시간이 정말로 실행중인 것을 가지고 있고하지 않습니다
know you might think that you have a late day Sun so on but these images get
당신은 당신이 그래서 늦은 하루 일을 생각할 수 있습니다 알고 있지만 이러한 이미지를 얻을
harder over time so you want to see those and so so start now likely so
시간이 지남에 열심히 그래서 당신은 그들을보고 싶어하고 그래서 그렇게 가능성이 지금 시작
there's no office hours or anything like that on Monday I'll hold make up office
월요일에는 근무 시간 또는 그런 아무것도 없다 내가 사무실을 만들 개최합니다
hours on Wednesday because I want you guys to be able to talk to me about the
수요일에 시간이 나는 너희들이에 대해 나에게 이야기 할 수 있도록하려면 때문에
special projects and so on so I'll be moving my office hours from Monday to
그래서 월요일부터 내 근무 시간 이동됩니다에 특별 프로젝트 등
wednesday usually I had my office starts at 6 p.m. instead I'll have them at 5
수요일은 일반적으로 내 사무실은 오후 6시 시작했다 대신 나는 5시에를해야합니다
p.m. and usually think gates 260 but now be engaged to 39-1 them both and yeah
오후 일반적으로는 게이트 (260)를 생각하지만 지금은 39-1 그들 모두와 약혼 할 예
and also to note when you're going to be studying for midterm that's coming up in
또한 당신이오고있어 중간에 대해 공부하려고 할 때주의해야
a few weeks
몇 주
make sure you go through the lecture notes as well which are really part of
당신이 정말로의 일부뿐만 아니라 강의 노트를 통해 이동해야합니다
this class and a kind of pick and choose some of the things that I think are most
이 클래스와 선택의 종류와 내가 가장 생각하는 것들 중 몇 가지를 선택
valuable to present a lecture but there's quite a bit of a more material
강의를 제공하는 귀중한하지만보다 재료의 꽤가있다
to beware of that might pop up in the mid term even though I'm comin some of
내가의 일부를오고 있어요에도 중기에 팝업을 생각하고 조심하는
the most important stuff usually no larger than URI through those lecture
그 강의를 통해 URI보다 일반적으로 더 큰 가장 중요한 물건
notes their complimentary to the actress and so the material for the material be
여배우에 자신의 무료 노트 등 재료의 재료가 될 수
drawn from both the lectures and its ok so having said all that we're going to
강의 양쪽에서 그려진 그 확인하여 모든 우리가 갈거야, 상기 한
dive into the material so where we are right now just as a reminder we have
재료에 뛰어 그래서 우리는 단지 우리가 미리 알림으로 바로 지금 어디에
this core function we looked at several loss functions such as the SP loss
이 핵심 기능은 우리가 같은 SP의 손실로 여러 손실 함수를 보았다
function last time and we look at the full lost that you achieve for any
기능 마지막으로 우리는 당신이 어떤을 위해 달성하는 것이 손실 전체를 보면
particular set of weights on over your training data and this loss made up of
특정 훈련 데이터에에 가중치의 세트로 구성이 손실
two components there's a data loss and loss right and really what we want to do
두 가지 구성 요소 우리가 무엇을 원하는 정말이 데이터 손실 및 손실 맞아 및
is we want to do right now the gradient expression of the loss of respect to the
우리가 지금에 대한 손실의 그라데이션 표현을하고 싶은 것입니다
weights and we want to do this so that we can actually perform the optimization
무게는 그리고 우리는 우리가 실제로 최적화를 수행 할 수 있도록이 작업을 수행 할 수
process optimization process we're doing in dissent where we iterate in a leading
우리가 선두에 반복 우리가 반대 의견에서하고있는 공정 최적화 과정
the gradient on your weights during a primary update and just repeating this
ㄱ 주 업데이트 중에 무게에 그라데이션과 그냥이 반복
over and over again so that were converging to
또 다시 이렇게 수렴 된 그
the low points on that loss function and when we arrived at a loss that's
저 그 손실 함수의 점과 우리가 손실에 도착했을 때의
equivalent to making good predictions over our training data in terms of this
이 측면에서 우리의 훈련 데이터에 대한 좋은 예측을하는 것과
course that come out now we also saw that are too kind of waste evaluate the
지금 나오는 과정은 우리는 또한 수 있습니다 너무 종류의 폐기물이 평가 보았다
gradient there's an American gradient and this is very easy to write but it's
그라데이션이 미국의 기울기 그리고이 작성하는 매우 간단하지만, 그것의
extremely slow to evaluate and there's an elegy gradient which is which you
극단적으로 평가 느리게하고있는이있는 비가 구배가있다
obtained by using calculus and will be going into that in this lecture quite a
수학을 사용하여 얻을이 강의에 그에 갈 것 꽤
bit more and so it's fast exact which is great but it's not you can get it wrong
좀 더하고 그래서 큰하지만 그렇지 당신이 잘못 얻을 수있어 어떤 빠르고 정확한이다
sometimes and so we always the following week already in check where we write all
때로는 그래서 우리는 항상 이미 검사에서 다음 주에 우리는 모든 쓰기 위치
the expressions to complete the analytic gradients and then we double check its
표현은 분석 그라디언트를 완료 한 후 우리는 다시 확인의
correctness with numerical gradient and so I'm not sure if you're going to see
수치 그라데이션 정확성 그리고 나는 당신이 볼 거라면 확실하지 않다
that you're going to see that definitely assignments ok so now you might be
당신은 당신이 할 수있는 지금이 확실히 확인 할당 볼 거라고
tempted to when you see the setup we just want to drive the gradient of the
이 설정을 볼 때 유혹 우리는 단지의 기울기를 구동 할
loss function back to the weights you might be tempted to just you know right
다시 당신은 단지에 유혹 될 수있는 가중치를 바로 알고에 손실 함수
out the full loss and just start to take the gradients as you seen your calculus
전체 손실 밖으로 당신이 당신의 미적분을 본 바로 그라데이션을 시작
class but I'd like to make is that you should think much more of this in terms
내가하고 싶습니다 클래스하지만 당신이 측면에서이 훨씬 더 생각해야한다는 것입니다
of computational grass instead of just taking thinking of one giant expression
대신 하나의 거대한 표현의 단지 복용 생각의 계산 잔디의
that you're going to drive content with pen and paper the expression for the
당신은 펜과 용지를위한 표현에 만족 구동 할 거라고
gradient and the reason for that
기울기 및 그 이유
so here we are thinking about these values flow flowing through a
그래서 여기에 우리는 흐르는 이러한 값에 대한 흐름을 생각하고
competition around these operations along circles and they transferred to
원을 따라 이러한 작업 주위에 경쟁과 그들에 전달
basically a function pieces that transform your inputs all the way to the
모든 방법으로 입력을 변환 기본적으로 기능 조각
loss function at the end so we start off with our data and our parameters as
마지막에 손실 함수는 그래서 우리는 우리의 데이터와 우리의 매개 변수로로 시작
inputs they feed through this competition graph which is just all
입력 그들은 단지 모든 인이 경쟁 그래프를 통해 공급
these series of functions along the way and at the end we get a single number
길을 따라와 말의 기능이 시리즈는 우리는 하나의 번호를
which is the loss and the reason that I'd like to think about it this way is
손실 난이 방법은 그것에 대해 생각하고자하는 이유는있다
that these expressions right now look very small and you might be able to
이러한 표현은 지금 매우 작은 보면 당신은 할 수있을 수 있음
derive these grievance but these expressions are in competition grass are
이러한 고충을 유도하지만, 이러한 표현은 경쟁 잔디되어 있습니다
about to get very big and so for example convolutional neural networks will have
매우 큰 얻을에 대한 그래서 예를 들어 길쌈 신경 네트워크는 것
hundreds maybe are dozens of operations so we'll have all these images
수백 어쩌면 우리 모두가 이러한 이미지를해야하므로 작업의 수십입니다
flow-through like big computational graph to get our loss and so it becomes
우리의 손실을 얻기 위해 큰 계산 그래프처럼-을 통해 흐름 등이된다
impractical to just write out these expressions and commercial networks are
바로 이러한 표현을 쓸 비현실적 및 상업 네트워크는
not even the worst of it once you actually start to for example do
심지어 당신은 실제로 예를 들어 수행에 최악 시작되지 일단
something called an alternate sheen which is a paper from the mind where
마음 어디에서 용지 인 대체 광택이라는 것을
this is basically differentiable Turing machine
이것은 기본적으로 미분 튜링 기계
so the whole thing is differentiable the whole procedure that the computer is
그래서 전부는 컴퓨터가하는 모든 절차 미분이다
performing on the tape is made smooth and is differentiable computer basically
테이프에 수행이 원활하게 이루어지고 미분 컴퓨터는 기본적으로
and the competition graphic this is huge and not only is this this is not hit
및 경쟁 그래픽이이이 명중되지 거대하고뿐만 아니라
because what you end up doing and we're going to recurrent neural networks and a
당신이 일을 끝낼 우리가 재발 신경망과에가는거야 무엇 때문에
bit but what you end up doing is you end up controlling this graph so think about
비트하지만 당신은 결국 일을 당신이이 그래프 그렇게 생각 제어 끝입니다
this graph copied many hundreds of time steps and so you end up with this giant
이 그래프는 시간 단계의 수백을 복사 그래서 당신은이 거대한 끝낼
monster of hundreds of thousands of nodes and little computational units and
수천 개의 노드와 약간의 계산 단위의 수백의 몬스터와
so it's impossible to write out you know here's the loss for the neural Turing
그래서 당신이 알고 쓰는 데 신경 튜링에 대한 손실 불가능이다
machine it's just impossible it would take like billions of pages and so we
기계 그것은 페이지의 수십억 우리과 같이 걸릴 것 단지 불가능
have to think about this more in terms of the structure so little functions
더 구조의 관점 너무 작은 기능에 이것에 대해 생각해야
transforming intermediate variables to just lost at the very end so we're going
우리는거야 그래서 중간 변수를 변환하는 것은 바로 맨 끝에 분실하기
to be looking specifically at competition graphs and how we can derive
경쟁 그래프에서 구체적으로보고 할 우리는 어떻게 유도 할 수있다
the gradient on the inputs with respect to the loss function at the very end so
맨 끝에 손실 함수에 대한 입력에 기울기 때문에
what start-up simple and concrete a very small competition graph we have three
시작 - 무슨 간단하고 구체적인 아주 작은 경쟁 그래프를 우리는 세 가지가
scalars as an input to this graph XY and Z and they take on these specific about
이 그래프 XY 및 Z에 대한 입력으로 스칼라 그들은 약이 특정에 걸릴
these in this example of negative 25 of 94 and we have this very small graphic
94의 마이너스 25의 예에서 이러한 우리는이 매우 작은 그래픽이
or circuit you'll hear me refer to these interchangeably hi there is a graph for
또는 당신이 날이 상호 교환 안녕을 참조 듣게 회로에 대한 그래프가
a circuit so we have this graph that at the end gives us this out the negative
회로는 그래서 우리는 마지막에 음을 우리에게 이것을 제공하는 것이이 그래프를
12 ok so here's what I've done is up over deep refilled look will call the
12 그래서 여기에 확인 내가 무슨 짓을했는지하는 동안 깊은 리필 모습은를 호출까지입니다입니다
forward pass of this graph where I set the input and then I compute the outfits
내가 입력을 설정 한 다음 나는 복장을 계산이 그래프의 전진 패스
and I would like to do as we'd like to drive the gradients of the expression on
그리고 나는 우리가에 식의 기울기를 구동하고 싶은대로 할 싶습니다
the inputs and what we'll do that is introduced this intermediate variable
입력과 우리가 그 무엇을 할 거 야이 중간 변수를 도입
cue the plus gate so there's a plus gate and times gate as I refer to them and
내가 그들에게 참조로 플러스 게이트 및 시간 게이트가 그래서 플러스 게이트 큐와
thus must get this computing this outfit cue and Sookie was this intermediate as
따라서이 컴퓨팅이 옷 큐를 얻고 수키는이 중간이었다합니다
a result of X plus Y and then f is a multiplication of qnz what I've written
내가 작성한 것을 다음 X 플러스 Y와의 결과는 f를 qnz의 곱셈이다
out here is what we want is the gradients the derivative stiff idea if I
여기에서 우리가 원하는 것은 그라디언트 파생 뻣뻣한 생각입니다 경우 I
do I get my desired and I've written out the intermediate please log gradients
내 원하는받을 수 있나요 나는 중간 로그인하시기 바랍니다 그라데이션을 작성했습니다
for every one of these two expressions separately so now we've performed for
우리가 수행 한 개별적으로 지금이 두 표현 모두를위한
class going from left to right and what will do now is will derive the backward
에서가 클래스는 왼쪽에서 오른쪽으로 지금 무엇을 할 것 인 것은 역을 유도합니다
pass will go from the back
패스 뒤쪽에서 이동합니다
to the front competing gradients of all the intermediates in our circuit until
앞으로 우리의 회로까지 모든 중간체의 그라디언트 경쟁
the very end we're going to build up to it the gradients on the inputs and so we
맨 끝에 우리는 그라디언트 입력에 그리고 우리 그것을 구축하는거야
start off at the very right and as a base case sort of this recursive
맨 오른쪽이 재귀의 기본 케이스의 일종으로 시작
procedure we're considering the gradient of the respective so this is just the
절차 우리는 각각의 기울기를 고려하고 그래서 이것은 단지입니다
identity function so what is the derivative of it
식별 기능은 그래서 그것의 파생 무엇인가
identity mapping the idea it's one right so in the identity has a gradient of one
그것은 정체성 바로 그래서 하나의 아이디어를 매핑 ID는 하나의 기울기가
so that's our base case we start off with the one and now we're going to go
그래서 우리가 하나를 시작하고 지금 우리가 갈거야 우리의 기본 사건
backwards through this graph so we want to gradient of with respect is that so
존경 그 너무 거꾸로이 그래프를 통해 우리는 그라데이션 할
what is that in this competition graph ok it's so we have not written out right
이 경쟁 그래프에서 확인이 그래서 우리는 권리를 작성하지 않은 있다는 것입니다
here and what is key in this particular example it's three right so the gradient
여기에 무엇이 특정 예제의 핵심은 세 가지 바로 그라데이션이되도록있어
on that according to this will become just 3 I'm going to be right ingredients
그에이에 따라 내가 바로 재료가 될거야 불과 3이 될 것이다
under the lines in red and the values are in green about the lines of the
빨간색 선과 값 아래의 라인에 대한 녹색에
gradient on the in the front is one and not the gradient onset is 33 as telling
전면의 그라데이션은 하나가 아닌 그라데이션 발병 텔링으로 33
you really intuitively keep in mind the interpretation of a gradient is what
당신은 정말 직관적으로 그라데이션의 해석은 무엇을 염두에 두어야
that's saying is that the influence of dead on the final value is positive and
즉 말하는 최종 값에 죽은의 영향이 긍정적이라고하고
with sort of course of three so if I increments Z by a small amount eight
세 코스의 종류와 그래서 소량의 팔에 의해 Z를 증가하는 경우
then the output of the circuit will react by increasing because it's a
그 회로의 출력은 a를 증가 때문에 반응
positive three will increase by three so small change will result in a positive
긍정적 세 긍정적 발생합니다 세 이렇게 작은 변화로 증가
change in the ultimate now the gradient upon cue in this case will be so deified
궁극적 인 변화는 이제이 경우 큐에 따라 기울기가 너무 신격화한다
IQ is that what is that before so we get a gradient of negative for on that part
IQ는 그 어떤 것을 우리는 그 부분에 대한 음의 기울기를 얻을 수 있도록하기 전에
of the circuit and with that saying is that if he were to increase the output
그 말과 회로 그리고 그가 인 경우 출력을 증가시키는 것입니다
of the circuit will decrease ok by if you increase by H be up to the circuit
회로가 좋아 감소 당신은 H 증가하는 경우가 회로까지 일
will decrease by four age that's the slope is negative for ok now we're going
기울기의 네 나이가 감소하는 것은 지금 우리가 가고있는 확인에 대한 부정적
to continue this process through this plus gate and this is where things get
이 플러스 게이트를 통해이 과정을 계속이 일을 얻을 수있는 곳입니다하기
slightly
약간
I suppose so we'd like to compute the agreement on on why with respect to Y
나는 우리가 Y에 대한 이유에에 계약을 계산하고 싶습니다 가정
and so the gradient on why would this in this particular graph will become
등 그라데이션 왜이 특정 그래프이 될 것이다 것
glass at it either way I'd like to think about this is by applying trainable ok
어느 쪽이든 내가 이것에 대해 생각하고 싶습니다 그것에 유리 학습 가능한 확인을 적용하는 것입니다
so the chain rule says that if you would like to direct the gradient of everyone
그래서 체인 규칙은 모든 사람의 기울기를 직접 할 것인지 말한다
why then it's equal to the FBI dq times the cube ideal i right and so we
왜 그때 내가 바로 그래서 우리 연방 수사 국 (FBI)의 DQ 시간에 큐브 이상적인 동일입니다
computed both of those expressions in particular IQ might be why we know is
우리가 알고 이유 일 수 있습니다 특정 IQ에서 그 표현을 모두 계산
negative or so that's the effect of the influence of coupon is DFID Q which is
음 정도 그 쿠폰의 영향의 효과가있어입니다 DFID의 Q입니다
negative for and now we know the local would like to know the local influence
부정적인 지금 우리가 지방을 알고는 로컬 영향을 알고 싶습니다
of why on cuba and that local influence of light on Q is one that's the locals
왜 Q에 빛의 로컬 영향 쿠바에 그의 것은 지역 주민을의 하나입니다
refer to as the local derivative of Y for the prostate and so the general
전립선에 대한 Y의 로컬 유도체 등 일반으로 참조
tells us that the correct thing to do to change these two gradients the local
정확한 것은이 두 그라디언트에게 지역을 변경 할 것을 우리에게 알려줍니다
gradient awful why don't you and the kind of global gradient of Q on the
그라데이션 끔찍한 왜 당신과의 Q의 글로벌 그라데이션의 종류하지
update of the circuit is to multiply them so we'll get made it four times and
우리가 네 번 만든거야 그래서 회로의 업데이트를 곱하는 것입니다
so this kind of the the crux of her back propagation works is this is a very
그래서 그녀를 다시 전파의 요점 이런 종류의이 매우이다 작동
important to understand here that we had at least two pieces that we keep
중요한 우리는 우리가 계속 적어도 두 가지를 한 것으로 여기에 이​​해하기
multiplying through when we performed as general we have computed X plus Y and
우리가 일반적으로 수행하는 경우를 통해 곱 우리는 X 플러스 Y와를 계산 한
the derivative X&Y with respect to that single expression is one and one so keep
그 하나의 표현에 대한 미분 X & Y는 하나 하나 그렇게 계속하다
in mind interpretation of the gradient that's saying is that X&Y have a
말하는 그라디언트의 마음의 해석에 X & Y가있을 것입니다
positive influence on cue with a slope of 10 increasing X by H
(10)의 기울기 H X가 증가함에 따라 큐에 긍정적 인 영향
will increase cue by H and eventually like as we'd like to influence of light
H에 의해 큐 증가하고 결국 같은처럼 우리는 빛의 영향을하고 싶습니다
on the final out but the circuit and so the way this end up working is you take
최종 밖으로하지만, 회로 등 길에이를 최대 작업은 걸릴 것입니다
the influence of why are you and we know the influence of Q on the final loss
의 영향을하고 우리는 최종 손실에 대한 Q의 영향을 알고 왜
which is what we are recursively computing here through this graph and
인 우리가 반복적으로이 그래프를 통해 여기 컴퓨팅 무엇을하고
the correct thing to do is to multiply them so we end up with a nickname for 10
할 수있는 올바른 것은 우리가 (10)의 별명으로 끝낼 수 있도록를 곱하는 것입니다
to 15 negative for and so the way this works out is basically what this is
15 음과 그래서 이것은 밖으로 작동 방식은 기본적으로 이것이 무엇인가
saying is that the influence of why on the final output circuit is negative or
속담 최종 출력 회로에 대한 이유의 영향을 부정하는 것이거나
so increasing why should decrease the album circuit by negative four times the
왜 부정적인 네 배 앨범 회로를 감소시켜야 증가
law change that you've made and the way that end up working out is why has a
가 왜 법 당신이 만든 변화와 운동을 끝낼 방법입니다
positive influence in Cuse increasing why slightly increase askew
약간 비스듬히 증가 이유를 증가 Cuse에 긍정적 인 영향
which likely decreases in the circuit so chain rule is kind of giving us this
어떤 체인의 규칙이 종류의 우리에게주는되도록 가능성이 회로 감소
correspondence
일치
we're going to get into this you'll see many many many associations of this and
우리가이 많은 많은 많은 연결을 볼 수 있습니다이 당신에받을거야 및
all drill this into you by the end of class and you understand it you will not
모든 클래스의 말에 당신이 점을 드릴 당신이 그것을 이해는하지 않습니다
have any symbolic expressions anywhere once we complete this letter actually
우리가 실제로이 편지를 완료하면 어디서나 어떤 상징적 인 표현이
implementing this and you'll see implementations of it later in this in
이 구현 당신은이 이후에 그것의 구현을 볼 수 있습니다
this it will always be just factors in numbers
항상있을 것입니다 이것은 단지 숫자 요인
robert is numbers ok and looking at X we have a very smart that happen thing that
로버트 숫자 확인 및 X보고 우리가 일을 어떻게하는 아주 똑똑한를하다
happens we wonder if IDX that's our final objective but we have to combine
우리는 우리의 최종 목표이다 그 IDX 궁금 발생하지만 우리는 결합해야
it we know what the exes what is access and listen to you and ask you same place
그것은 우리가 접근이 무엇인지 무엇 예전 친구를 알고 당신을 듣고 당신에게 같은 장소를 물어
on the end of the circuit and so that ends up being the chain grow so take a
체인이 그렇게을 성장 될 수있을 테니까요 때문에 회로의 끝에서
negative four times want to give you one ok so the way this works to generalize a
음 네 번 당신이이 일반화 작동하는 방식 때문에 하나의 확인을주고 싶어
bit from this example and way to think about it is as follows you are a gate
당신이 게이트입니다 다음과 같이이 예제와 방법에서 비트는이에 대해 생각하는
embedded in a circuit and this is a very large computational graph or circuit and
회로에 삽입이 매우 큰 계산 그래프 또는 회로이며
you receive some templates some particular numbers X&Y come in and
당신은 어떤 특정 번호 X & Y가 와서 몇 가지 템플릿을 수신하고,
perform some operation on them and compute some good set Z and now this
그들에 대한 몇 가지 작업을 수행하고 좋은 세트 Z를 계산하고 지금이
magazine goes into competition grass and something happens to it but you're just
잡지는 경쟁 잔디로 전환 무언가가 일어나는하지만 당신은 그냥있어
too great hanging out in a circuit and you're not sure what happens but by the
너무 큰 회로에서 놀고 당신은이 아니라 무슨 확실하지 않다
end of the circuit the loss computed and that's the forward pass and then we're
우린 다음 회로의 끝은 손실을 계산하고 그 전진 패스 그리고
proceeding recursively in the reverse order backwards but before that actually
거꾸로 역순으로 반복적으로 진행하지만, 실제로 전
get to that part right away when I get X&Y the thing I'd like to point out that
나는 X & Y 내가하고 싶은 일이 있다는 지적에 도착하면 바로 그 부분에 도착
during the forward pass if you're this gate and you get to your values X&Y you
전진 패스 동안이 게이트 있다면 당신은 당신의 값 X & Y 당신에 도착
computer output said and there's another thing you can computer right away and
컴퓨터 출력과 상기 다른 일이있다 할 수 있습니다 컴퓨터에 바로와
that is the local gradients
그 지역 그라디언트입니다
X&Y so I can compute those right away because I'm just a gate and I know what
X & Y 그래서 바로 그냥 게이트이기 때문에 사람들을 계산할 수 있습니다 내가 알고있는
I'm performing like say additional application so I know the influence that
내가 좋아하는 수행하고있어 추가 응용 프로그램은 내가 영향을 알고 말을 그
X&Y have won my out the body so I can compute those guys right away but then
X & Y 그래서 지금 당장하지만 그 사람들을 계산할 수 있습니다 내 밖으로 몸을 이겼다
what happens
무슨 일이야
near the end so the lawsuits computed another going backwards eventually learn
끝 부분에서 계산 된 소송은 다른 결국 배울 뒤로 갈 수 있도록
about what is my influence on
내 영향에 무엇인가에 대한
the final output of the circuit the loss to learn what is DL by these in their
회로의 최종 출력 DL은 이들에 의해 손쉽게 배울 수있는 손실 자신의
ingredient will flow into me and what I have to do is I have to change that
성분은 내게로 흘러 제가해야 할 일은 내가 그 변경해야 할 것입니다 것입니다
gradient through this recursive case so I have to make sure to change the
나는를 변경할 수 있는지 확인해야합니다 있도록이 재귀 경우를 통해 그라데이션
gradient through my operation performed and it turns out that the correct thing
내 작업을 통해 그라데이션을 수행하고 정확한 것은 밝혀
to do here buy tramadol really what it's saying is the correct thing to do is to
여기에서이 말하는 정말 무슨 트라마돌을 구입하는 것은이다 할 올바른 일이
multiply your local gradient without gradient and that actually gives you the
그라데이션없이 해당 지역의 그라데이션을 곱 것을 실제로 당신에게 제공하는
DL IDX
DL IDX
employees off X on the final output of the circuit so really chain rule is just
회로의 최종 출력에 X 오프 직원 그래서 정말 체인 규칙은 그냥
this added multiplication where we take what are called Global gradient of this
우리는이 글로벌 그라데이션이라고 무엇을 가지고이 추가 곱셈
gate on the outfit and we've changed through the local gradient in the same
의상에 게이트와 우리는 같은에서 로컬 그라데이션을 변경했습니다
thing goes for a while so it's just a multiplication of that guy the gradient
그것은 그 사람 그라디언트의 단지 곱셈 그래서 것은 잠시 동안 간다
by your local gradient if you're a gate and then remember that these X's and Y's
해당 지역의 그라데이션으로 당신은 게이트있어 다음 기억한다면 이들 X 년대와 Y의
there are coming from different states right so you end up with the cursing
당신이 저주로 끝날 바로 그래서 다른 상태에서이오고있다
this process through the entire cup additional Turkish and so these gates
추가 터키어 등이 게이트 전체 컵을 통해이 과정
just basically communicate to each other the influence on the final loss so they
다만 기본적 그들이 그렇게 마지막 손실에 서로 영향을 통신
tell each other ok if this is a positive gradient that means you're positively
이것은 당신이 긍정적있어 의미 긍정적 인 그라데이션 경우 서로 확인 말해
influencing the loss of its negative gradient negative influence negatively
부정적인 부정적인 그라데이션 부정적인 영향의 손실에 영향을 미치는
influencing loss and he just gets almost applied through the circuit by these
손실에 영향을 미치는 그는 단지 거의 이들에 의해 회로를 통해 적용됩니다
local gradients and you end up with and this process is called back propagation
지역 그라디언트와 함께 결국이 과정은 전파 다시 호출
it's a way of computing through a recursive application of chain rule
그것은 연쇄 규칙 재귀 적용하여 계산하는 방법이다
through competition grab the influence of every single intermediate value in
경쟁을 통해 하나 하나 중간 값의 영향에 잡아
that graph on the final loss function and so will see many examples of this
최종 손실 함수 등이 그래프는이 많은 예제를 볼 수 있습니다
truck is like her I'll go into a specific example there is a slightly
트럭 내가 약간이 구체적인 예에​​ 갈거야 그녀처럼
larger and we'll work through it in detail but i dont their own questions at
더 큰 우리가 구체적으로 그것을 통해 작동합니다하지만 난에 자신의 질문을 해달라고
this point that I would like to ask ahead I'm going to come back to that you
내가 좋아하는 것,이 점은 내가 당신에게 돌아올거야 앞서 물어
add the gradients the grading the cognitive Adam so if Z is being employed
Z가 사용되는 경우 있도록 등급에게 그라디언트에게인지 아담를 추가
in multiple places in the circus the back roads closed will add that will
서커스의 여러 장소에서 다시 도로는 그 뜻을 추가합니다 폐쇄
come back to that point
그 시점에 돌아온다
like we're going to get the all of those issues and we're gonna see ya you're
같은 우리가 그 문제의 전부를받을거야 그리고 우리는거야 당신이있어 나중에 참조
gonna get what we call banishing gradient problems and so on
거야 우리가 그라데이션 문제를 추방 호출 것을 얻을
we'll see let's go through another example to make this more concrete so
우리의이보다 구체적인 그렇게하기 위해 또 다른 예를 통해 풀어 볼 수 있습니다
here we have another circuit it happens to be computing a little two-dimensional
여기에 우리가 그런 일이 다른 회로는 작은 두 개의 차원을 계산해야 할
in Iran but for now don't worry about that interpretation just think of this
이란에서하지만 지금은 그냥이 생각하는 그 해석에 대해 걱정하지 마십시오
as that's an expression so one over one-plus key to the whatever number of
그 표현 때문에 하나를 통해 하나의 플러스 키의 어떤 숫자의로
inputs here is by Andrew function and we have a single output over there and I
여기에 입력 앤드류 기능에 의해 그리고 우리는 저기 내가 단일 출력이
translated that mathematical expression into this competition in draft form so
초안 형태 때문에이 대회에 수식 것을 번역
we have to recursively from inside out compete with expression so a person do
그래서 사람이 할 식으로 우리가 안에서부터 밖으로 재귀에있는 경쟁
all the little W times access and then we add them all up and then we take a
모든 작은 W 시간에 액세스하고 우리는 그들 모두를 추가 한 다음 우리는을
negative of it and then we exponentially that and they had one and then we
그것의 부정적이고 우리는 기하 급수적으로 그들은했다 하나, 그리고, 우리
finally divide and we get the result of the expression and so we're going to do
마지막으로 나누어 우리는 식의 결과를 얻을 그래서 우리가 할거야
now is we're going to back propagate through this expression we're going to
지금 우리가 가고있는이 식을 통해 전파를 백업하는거야입니다
compute what the influence of every single input value is on the output of
매 입력 값의 영향의 출력에 손쉽게 계산
this expression that is degrading here
여기 저하되어이 식
so for now the US is just a binary plus its entirety + gate and we have a plus
그래서 지금 미국은 플러스 전체 + 게이트 이진 그리고 우리는 플러스가
one gate I'm making up these gates on the spot and we'll see that what is a
하나의 게이트 나는 그 자리에서이 문을 만들고있어 우리는 어떤이는 것을 볼 수 있습니다
gate or is not a gate is kind of up to you come back to this point of it so for
게이트 또는 게이트가 당신에게 달려 가지이다 아니다를위한 그래서이 시점에 돌아온다
now I just like we have several more gates that we're using throughout and so
지금은 단지 우리가 우리가 전반에 걸쳐 그래서 사용하는 몇 가지 더 게이트가 좋아
I just like to write out as we go through this example several of these
난 그냥 우리가 이들 중 몇 가지 예를 통해 이동으로 쓰는 좋아
derivatives exponentiation and we know for every little local gate what these
파생 상품 지수 그리고 우리는 모든 작은 지역의 게이트에 대해 알고있는이
local gradients are right so we can do that using calculus so the extra tax and
지역 그라디언트를 잘 그래서 우리가 할 수있는되는 미적분을 사용하여 추가 세금이 너무과
so on so these are all the operations and also addition and multiplication
그래서 이러한 있도록 모든 작업과 덧셈과 곱셈이다
which I'm assuming that you have memorized in terms of what the great
나는 당신이 어떤 위대한 측면에서 기억했다고 믿고있어하는
things look like they're going to start off at the end of the circuit and I've
그들은 회로의 끝에서 시작하는거야 같은 것들을 모양과 나는했습니다
already filled in a one point zero zero in the back because that's how we always
이미 뒷면에 원 포인트 제로 제로 채워 그건 어떻게 항상 있기 때문에
start this recursion
이 재귀를 시작
1110 right but since that's the gradient on the identity function now we're going
1110 오른쪽하지만 그 신원 기능에 그라데이션 지금 이후 우리는거야
to back propagate through this one over x operation ok so the relative of one of
하나의 상대적 그래서 확인 X 작업을 통해이 일을 통해 전파를 백업하기
wrecks the local gradient is a negative one over x squared so that none of Rex
로컬 그라데이션이 X를 통해 음의 하나가 렉스의 그래서 아무도 제곱되지 난파
gate during the forward pass received input 1.37 and right away that one of
게이트는 앞으로 통과하는 동안 입력 1.37을 받고 즉시 중 하나가
her ex Kate could have computed what the local gradients the local variant was
그녀의 전 케이트 계산 한 수 로컬 변형은 지역 그라디언트 것이었다
negative one over x squared and ordering back propagation and has to buy tramadol
X를 통해 음의 하나는 제곱과 전파를 다시 주문 및 트라마돌을 구입한다
multiply that local gradient by the gradient of it on the final of the
의 마지막에의 경사가 그 로컬 기울기를 곱할
circuit which is easy because it happens to be so what ends up being the
쉽게 회로는 그렇게 무엇 인 끝을 될 일이 있기 때문에
expression for the back propagated reading here from one of my ex Kate
뒷면에 대한 표현은 내 전 케이트 중 하나를 여기에 읽기 전파
but she always has two pieces local gradient times the gradient from or from
하지만 그녀는 항상 두 가지 지역 그라데이션 배에서 또는에서 기울기가
which is the gradient DFID X so that that is the local gradient
이는 그 로컬 구배가되도록 기울기 DFID X입니다
giving one over 3.7 squared and then multiplied by one point zero which is
3.7 이상 하나의 제곱 한 다음 하나 포인트 0으로 곱한 제공
degrading from which is really just one because we just started and so applying
있는 분해하는 것은 정말 우리가 시작했기 때문에 하나 때문에 적용입니다
general right away here and the other is negative 01534 that's the gradient on
일반적으로는 바로 여기에 다른 하나는 구배에있어 그 01534 음
that piece of the wire where this valley was blowing ok so it has a negative
이 계곡은 확인 불고 된 와이어의 조각은 그래서 음이
effect on the outfit you might expect that right because if you were to
당신에게 당신이 있다면 바로 때문에 기대할 수있는 복장에 효과
increase this value and then it goes through a gate of one over x then
이 값이 증가하고 그 후 X 위에 하나의 게이트를 통과
increased amount of Rex get smaller so that's why you're seeing negative
그 이유는 당신이 부정적인보고있는, 그래서 렉스의 증가 금액은 작아
gradient rate we're going to continue back propagation here in the next gate
그라데이션 속도는 우리는 다음 게이트 여기에 전파를 다시 계속거야
in the circuit it's adding a constant of one so the local gradient if you look at
당신이 보면 회로에서 하나의 일정한 때문에 로컬 그라데이션을 추가하는 것
adding a constant to a value the gradient off on exit is just one right
출구에 값으로 기울기를 일정을 추가하면 하나의 권리
to talk to us and so the change gradient here that we continue along the wire
우리에게 이야기하고 그래서 여기에 변화 구배 우리는 선을 따라 계속합니다
will be your local gradient which has one time the gradient from above the
상기에서 그라데이션을 한 시간이 해당 지역의 그라데이션 될 것입니다
gate which it has just learned is negative Jul 23 2013 continues along the
그냥 배운 게이트 부정적인 2013년 7월 23일가 함께 계속됩니다
way are unchanged and intuitively that makes sense right because this is value
방법 변경되지 않습니다 직관적 즉,이 값이 바로 때문에 의미가 있습니다
floats and it has some influence on the final circuit and if you're if you're
수레 그리고 마지막 회로에 어떤 영향을하고 있다면 당신이 있다면
adding one then its influence its rate of change of slope toward the final
그 영향력 후 최종쪽으로 기울기의 변화의 속도를 하나 추가
value doesn't change if you increase this by some amount the effect at the
당신이 어떤 양만큼의 효과를이 증가하는 경우 값은 변경되지 않습니다
end will be the same because the rate of change doesn't change through the +1
변화율이 1을 변경하지 않기 때문에 일단은 동일 할 것이다
gays just a constant officer continued innovation here so the gradient of the
게이는 일정한 장교의 기울기 때문에 여기에 혁신을 계속
axe the axe so you can come back propagation we're going to perform
우리가 수행하는거야 전파를 돌아올 수 있도록 도끼 도끼
gates input of negative one
음 하나의 게이트 입력
it right away could have completed its local gradient and now it knows that the
그것은 바로 로컬 그라데이션을 완료 할 수 지금은 것​​을 알고
gradient from above is negative point by three so the continued backpropagation
위의 그라데이션이 세 가지 때문에 계속 역 전파에 의해 음의 포인트입니다
here in applying chain rule would received the rhetorical questions I'm
여기에 체인 규칙을 적용하는 것 난 수사학 질문을 받았다
not sure but but basically each of the negative one which is the ex the ex
확실하지만,하지만, 기본적으로 전이 전 인 부정적인 하나의 각을하지
input to this expert eight times the chain rule right to the point by three
권리 세에 의해 지점이 전문가에 입력 8 배 체인 규칙
so we keep multiplying their own so what is the effect on me and what I have an
그래서 우리는 자신을 곱 계속 이렇게 나에 미치는 영향은 무엇이고 나는 무슨이
effect on the final end of the circuit those are being always multiplied so we
그 회로의 최종 끝에 효과는 항상 우리가 곱되고있다
get negative 22 at this point so now we have a time to negative one gate so what
그래서 지금이 시점에서 마이너스 22를 얻을 우리는 부정적인 하나의 게이트에 시간이 그래서 뭐
ends up happening what happens to the gradient when you do it turns me on an
그것이 나를집니다 당신이 할 때 그라데이션 일어나는 일이 끝납니다
accomplished on da lips around right because we have basically constant input
우리는 기본적으로 일정 입력을 가지고 있기 때문에 바로 주위에 다 입술에 달성
which happened to be a constant of negative one so negative one time one
그래서 음의 음 하나 하나 시간을 일정하게 일어난 어느
time they dont give us negative one in the forward pass and so now we have to
시간 그들은 전진 패스로 우리에게 부정적인 하나를 제공 해달라고 그래서 지금 우리에게있다
multiply by a that's the local gradient times the greeting from Bob which is
인 밥에서 인사말 로컬 그라데이션 시간을의하는 곱
fine too so we end up with just positive so now continue back propagation
미세 너무 그래서 우리는 지금 그냥 긍정적으로 끝낼 전파를 다시 계속
propagating + and this plus operation has multiple input here the green in the
전파 +이 플러스 작업은 여러 여기에 입력에 녹색이
local gradient for the bus gate as one and 10 what ends up happening to the
하나는 10 버스 게이트 현지 그라데이션은 무엇 일어나고 끝
brilliance flow along the upper buyers
상단 구매자 따라 광택 흐름
surplus paid has a local gradient on all of its always will be just one because
지불 잉여는 모든 로컬 그라데이션이 항상 하나 때문에이됩니다
if you just have a functioning you know experts why then for that function the
당신은 단지 기능이있는 경우 해당 기능에 대한 이유를 다음 전문가를 알고
gradient on either X or Y is just one and so what you end up getting is just
X 또는 Y 중 하나에 그라데이션은 하나이며, 그래서 당신은 점점 끝날 것입니다
one time spent two and so in fact for a plus gate always see see the same fact
한 시간은 2 시간에 그렇게 더하기 게이트에 대한 사실 항상 같은 사실을보고 참조
where the local gradient all of its inputs is one and so whatever grading it
모든 입력의 로컬 그라데이션 하나 때문에 어디를 무엇을 등급
gets from above it just always distributes gradient equally to all of
그냥 항상 모두에게 동등하게 그라데이션을 배포 이상에서 가져옵니다
its inputs because in the chain rule don't have multiplied and multiplied by
그 입력은 체인 규칙 곱하지 않고 승산 때문에
10 something remains unchanged surplus get this kind of like ingredient
10 일이 변경되지 않은 잉여는 같은 성분의이 종류를 얻을 남아
distributor whereas something flows in from the top it all just spread out all
뭔가 반면 유통은 모든 단지 모든 퍼져 상단에서 유입
the great teams equally to all of its children and so we've already received
위대한 팀은 동등하게 모든 자식과 우리는 이미받은
one of the inputs gradient point to hear on the very final output of the circuit
입력 그라데이션 포인트 중 하나는 회로의 최종 출력에 매우 듣고
and so this employees has been completed through a series of applications of
그래서이 직원의 애플리케이션 일련 완료
trainer along the way there was another plus get that skipped over and so this
트레이너 길을 따라가 다른이었다 플러스 그 이상 등이 생략 얻을
point you kind of this tribute to both 20.2 equally so we've already done a
모두 20.2이 공물의 당신 종류를 가리 동일하게 우리가 이미 수행 한
blockade and there's a multiply get there and so now we're going to back
봉쇄하고있다 곱셈 거기 그래서 지금 우리는 다시거야
propagate through that multiply operation and so the local grade so the
그 곱셈 연산을 통해 전파 등 지역 학년 때문에
so what will be the gradient for w 00 will be degrading 40 basically
기본적으로 40 저하됩니다 00w에 대한 그래서 무슨 일이 그라데이션이됩니다
2000 you will be going in W one will be W 0:30 will be negative one times when
2000 당신은 한 번 할 때 음수가 될 것이다 0시 반 (W) 될 것 W 하나에 갈 것
too good and the gradient on x zero will be there is a bug bite away in the slide
너무 좋은있을 것입니다 X 제로에 그라데이션 버그가 슬라이드에 떨어져 물린입니다
that I just noticed like few minutes before I actually create the class also
난 사실 또한 클래스를 작성하기 전에 나는 단지 몇 분처럼 발견하는 것이
increase starting to class so you see . 39 there it should be point for its
당신이 볼 수 있도록 클래스에 시작 증가한다. 39이 그것에 대한 포인트가 될한다 그
because of a bug in evangelization because I'm truncating a to the small
때문에 복음화의 버그 난 작은로를 절단하고 있습니다 때문에
digits but basically that should be pointed or because the way you get that
숫자하지만 기본적으로 그 지적해야하거나 것을 얻는 방법 때문에
is two times pointed to get the point for just like I've written out there so
두 개의 시간은 내가 지금 거기 작성한처럼의 포인트를 얻을 수 지적
that's what the opportunity there okay so that we've been propagated the
우리는을 전파했습니다 있도록 그가 어떤 기회를 괜찮아
circuit here and we get through this expression and so you might imagine in
여기에 회로 우리는이 표현을 통해 얻을 그래서 당신의 상상
there are actual downstream applications will have data and all the parameters as
실제 다운 스트림 데이터를해야합니다 응용 프로그램 및 모든 매개 변수 등이있다
inputs loss functions at the top at the end it will be forward pass to evaluate
끝 상단 입력 손실 함수는 앞으로있을 평가할 합격
the loss function and then we'll back propagate through every piece of
손실 기능과 우리가 다시 것은 모든 조각을 통해 전파
competition we've done along the way and Welbeck propagate through every gate to
경쟁은 우리가 길을 따라 한 적이과 웰벡이에 대한 모든 게이트를 통해 전파
get our imports and back up again just means supply chain rule many many times
우리의 수입을 얻고 백업 다시 단지 공급 체인 규칙 많은 많은 시간을 의미
and we'll see how that is implemented in but the question i guess im going to
우리는 그에서 구현하는 방법을 볼 수 있지만, 문제는 내가 메신저에가는 것 같아요
skip that because it's the same I'm going to skip the other questions
이 같은이기 때문에 다른 질문을 건너 뛸거야 것을 이동
so the cost of forward and backward propagation is roughly almost always end
그래서 전후 전파의 비용은 대략 거의 항상 끝
up being basically equal when you look at timings usually the backup a slightly
기본적으로 같다고까지 당신은 일반적으로 백업 약간 타이밍을 볼 때
slower idea so let's see one thing I want to point out before in one is that
느린 생각은 그래서 하나가 있다는 것입니다 내가 이전에 지적하고 싶은 한 가지를 보자
the setting of these gates like these gates are arbitrary so what can I could
이 게이트 등이 게이트의 설정은 그래서 무엇을 할 수 내가 할 수있는 임의적
have known for example is some of you may know this I can collapse these gates
예를 들어 알고 당신 중 일부는 내가이 문을 축소 할 수 있습니다 이것을 알고있다
into one gate if I wanted to for example in something called the sigmoid function
하나의 게이트에 뭔가, 예를 들어 시그 모이 드 함수를 호출하고 싶다면
which has that particular form a single facts which the sigmoid function
이는 시그 모이 드 함수 특정 형태의 하나의 사실이있다
computes won over one plus or minus tax and so I could have rewritten that
하나 플러스 또는 마이너스 세금을 통해 원 계산하고 그래서 난 것을 다시 한 수
expression and i cant collapsed all of those gates that made up the sigmoid
표현은 내가 S 상을 만들어 그들 문을 모두 붕괴 캔트
gate into a single gate and so there's a sigmoid get here and I could have done
단일 게이트에 게이트 등 시그 모이 나는이 할 수 있었다 여기에 도착하고 있어요
that in a single go sort of and when I would have had to do if I wanted to have
내가하고 싶어하는 경우해야 할 일을했을 것이다 때 하나의 종류의 갈 것을
that gate as I need to compute an expression for how this so what is the
그 게이트 나는이 그래서 무엇 방법에 대한 식을 계산하기 위해 필요로하는
local gradient for the sigmoid get basically so what is the gradient of the
기본적으로 얻을 S 상 로컬 그라데이션 그래서의 기울기 무엇인가
small gate on its input and I had to go through some math which I'm not going to
작은 입력에 게이트와 내가 않을거야 일부 수학을 통과했다
go into detail but you end up with that expression over there
세부 사항으로 이동하지만 당신은 저기있는 식으로 끝날
it ends up being 1-6 next time segment of access to local gradient and that
이 지역의 기울기와 그 액세스의 1-6 다음 세그먼트 인 끝
allows me to put this piece into a competition graph because once I know
나 경쟁 그래프로이 조각을 넣을 수 있습니다 내가 아는 한 번 때문에
how to compute the local gradient everything else is defined just through
다른 지역 그라데이션 모든 단지를 통해 정의되는 방법을 계산하는 방법
chain rule and multiply everything together so we can back propagate
체인 규칙과 우리가 전파 백업 할 수 있도록 모든 것을 함께 곱
through the sigmoid get down and the way that would look like is input to the
S 상을 통해 내려와 같을 것이다 방법은에 입력되고,
gate was one point zero that's what flu went into the gate and punk 73 went out
게이트 독감 게이트에 가서 무엇을 하나 포인트 제로이었고, 펑크 73은 밖으로 나갔습니다
so . 7360 facts okay and we want to local gradient which is as we've seen
그래서. 7360 사실 좋아 그리고 우리는 우리가 본 것 같다 현지 그라데이션하려는
from the math on their backs so you get access point cemetery multiplying 1-23
자신의 허리에 수학에서 당신은 1-23 곱 액세스 포인트 묘지를 얻을 수 있도록
that's the local gradient and then times will work we happened to be at the end
즉, 로컬 그라데이션의 다음 번 우리가 마지막에 우연히 작동합니다
of the circuit so times 10 even writing so we end up with 12 and of course we
10도 작성 회로의 그렇게 시간은 그래서 우리는 12 물론 결국 우리
get the same answer
같은 답변을 얻을
point to as we received before 12 because calculus works but basically we
수학이 있지만, 기본적으로 작동하기 때문에 우리가 12 전에받은 가리킨 우리
could have broken up this expression down and
다운이 식을 부러 졌을 수 있으며,
one piece at a time or we could just have a single signaled gate and it's
한 번에 조각 또는 우리는 단지 하나의 신호 게이트를 가질 수 그것은이다
kind of up to us and what level up here are key to break these expressions and
종류의 어떤 수준까지 여기에 이​​러한 식을 깰 열쇠 우리에게 달려과과
so you'd like to
그래서 당신은하고 싶습니다
intuitively clustered these expressions into single gates if it's very efficient
그것은 매우 효율적인지 직관적으로 하나의 게이트에 이러한 식을 클러스터
or easy to direct the local radiance because then they become your pieces so
그들은 당신의 조각 그렇게 될 수 있기 때문에 또는 쉽게 로컬 윤기를 연출하는
the question is do libraries typically do that I do they worry about you know
문제는 일반적으로 당신이 알고에 대해 나는 그들이 걱정 않도록해야합니까 라이브러리입니다
what's what's easy to convince the computer and the answer is yes I would
어떤 컴퓨터를 설득 쉽게 무엇을하고 대답은 '예 나는 것입니다
say so so he noted that there are some piece of operation you'd like to do over
그래서 그래서 그는 당신을 통해 수행하려는 작업의 일부 조각이 있음을 지적 말
and over again and it has a very simple local gradient that's something very
또 다시 그리고 그것은 매우 뭔가 아주 간단한 로컬 그라데이션이
appealing to actually create a single unit of and we'll see some of those
실제로 단일 유닛을 만들 호소 우리는 그 중 일부를 볼 수 있습니다
examples actually but I think I'd like to also point out that once you the
예를 들면 실제로하지만 난 또한 지적하고 싶은 생각하면 한 번
reason I like to think about these compositional grass is it really hope
나는이 조성 잔디에 대해 생각하는 좋아하는 이유는 정말 희망입니다
your intuition to think about how greedy and slow in a neural network it's not
그렇지 않은 방법 욕심 느린 신경 네트워크에있는 당신의 직감에 대해 생각하는
just you don't want this to be a black box do you want to understand
당신이 당신이 이해 싶어 블랙 박스 싶지 않아
intuitively how this happens and you start to develop after a while of
직관적으로 어떻게 이런 일이 발생하면의 잠시 후에 개발 시작
looking at additional graphs intuitions about how these graybeards flow and this
이 graybeards 흐름이 방법에 대한 자세한 그래프 직관보고
might help you debug some issues like say will go to banish ingredient problem
말은 성분 문제를 추방하기 위해 갈 것 같은 당신이 어떤 문제를 디버깅하는 데 도움이 될 수
it's much easier to understand exactly what's going wrong in your optimization
그것은 무엇 최적화에 잘못된거야 정확히 이해하는 것이 훨씬 쉽게
if you understand how greedy and slow and networks will help you debug these
당신이 도움이 될 것입니다 얼마나 욕심과 느린 네트워크를 이해한다면 이러한 디버깅
networks much more efficiently and so some information for example we already
훨씬 더 효율적으로 네트워크와 우리는 이미 예를 들어, 그래서 몇 가지 정보
saw the eighth at Gate it has a little reading the one to all of its inputs so
그것의 입력 그래서 모두에게 하나를 읽고 조금이 게이트에서 여덟 번째를 보았다
it's just a greeting distributor that's like a nice way to think about it
그것은 그것에 대해 생각하는 좋은 방법처럼 그냥 인사 대리점입니다
whenever you have a plus operation anywhere in your score function or your
당신은 당신의 점수 기능 또는 어디 더하기 수술을 할 때마다
comment or anywhere else it's distributed ratings the max kate is
댓글을 다른 곳은 최대 케이트는 평가를 분산 있어요
instead a great writer and way this works is if you look at the expression
당신이 표현 보면 대신이 작품 훌륭한 작가와 방법은
like we have great these markers don't work so if you have a very simple binary
당신은 아주 간단한 바이너리가있는 경우 등 우리는 이러한 마커는 정말 대단 작동하지 않는 한
expression of Maxim XY so this is a gate then the gradient on x online if you
당신이 경우 맥심 XY의 표현은 그래서 이것은 온라인으로 다음 게이트 X의 기울기이다
think about it the green on the larger one of your inputs which is larger the
더 큰 당신의 입력의 큰 일에 대해 녹색을 생각한다
gradient on that guy is one and all this and the smaller one is a greeting of
그 사람에 그라데이션은 하나이며 모든 이것과 더 작은 하나의 인사말입니다
zero and intuitively that because if one of these was smaller than what it has no
제로 직관적으로 이들 때문에 경우 하나는 더이 무엇보다 작은 것을
effect on the out but because the other guy's larger and that's what ends up
다른 사람의 큰 및 그건 무슨 일이 끝나는 때문에 출력에 영향을하지만,
getting through the gate so you end up with a gradient of one on the
게이트를 통해 점점 당신은 하나의 구배로 끝날 수 있도록
larger one of the inputs and so that's why max cady as a gradient writer if I'm
입력 중 하나 크고 그래서 난 경우 그라데이션 작가로 왜 맥스 캐디의
actually and I have received several inputs one of them was the largest of
실제로 내가받은 여러 입력 그들 중 하나의 가장 큰했다
all of them and that's the value that I propagated through the circuit and
그들 모두 그 내가 회로를 통해 전파되는 값이고
application time I'm just going to receive my gradient from above and I'm
응용 프로그램 시간은 그냥 위에서 내 구배를받을거야 그리고 난
going to write it to whoever was my largest impact it's a gradient writer
나의 가장 큰 충격이었다 누구에 기록하려고하면은 그라데이션 작가의
and multiply gate is a gradient switcher actually don't think that's a very good
및 다중 게이트 그라데이션 스위처는 실제로 아주 좋은 생각하지 않습니다이다
way to look at it but I'm referring to the fact that it's not actually
방법은 그것을보고 할 수 있지만, 실제로는 아니에요 난 사실을 말하는 겁니다
nevermind about that part so the question is what happens if the two
신경 끄시 고 질문 그래서 그 부분에 대해 두 가지 경우 발생하는 것입니다
inputs are equal when you go through max Kade what happens I don't think it's
당신은 내가 그것을 생각하지 않습니다 무슨 일 최대 카데을 통과 할 때 입력은 동일하다
correct to distributed to all of them I think you have to you have to pick one
그들 모두에게 분배에 올바른 난 당신이 하나를 선택해야한다고 생각
that basically never happens in actual practice so max gradient here actually
즉, 기본적으로 결코 실제로 여기에 실제 연습 때문에 최대 구배를 발생하지 않습니다
have an example is that here was larger than W so only is it has an influence on
예를 들어 여기에 너무 만이 영향에가있다 (W)보다 큰 것을이다가
the output of this max Kade right so when two flows into the max gate and
이 최대 카데의 출력 바로 그렇게 할 때 최대 게이트로 두 흐름 및
gets read it and W gets a zero gradient because its effect on the circuit is
읽어와 회로에 효과가 있으므로 W가 0 구배를 얻는다 도착
nothing there is zero because when you change it doesn't matter when you change
아무것도 제로가없는 당신이 변경할 때 중요하지 않습니다를 변경할 때 때문에
it because that is not a larger bally going through the competition grounds I
그것은 그 경쟁 경내 I 통과하는 큰 발리 없기 때문에
have another note that is related to back propagation which we already
전파하는 우리는 이미 백업과 관련된 또 다른 메모가
addressed through question I just want to briefly point out with it terribly
난 그냥 간단히 정말 그것으로 지적하고 싶은 질문을 통해 해결
bad luck and figure that if you have these circuits and sometimes you have a
불운과 이러한 회로가있는 경우 때때로 당신은이 있는지 그림
value that branches out into a circuit and is used in multiple parts of the
값 회로에 지점 밖으로 그와의 여러 부분에 사용된다
circuit the correct thing to do by multivariate chain rule is to actually
정확한 것은 변수 체인 규칙에 의해 수행하는 회로는 사실이다
add up the contributions at the operation so gradients add a background
그라디언트 배경을 추가 할 수 있도록 동작에 기여를 추가
in backwards through the circuit if they ever flow in in these backward flow
회로를 통해 거꾸로 그들이 이제까지이 역류에 유입하는 경우
right we're going to go into implementation very simple just a couple
바로 우리는 매우 간단한 구현 단지 몇으로 갈거야
of questions
질문
thank you for the question the question is is there ever like a loop in these
질문은 질문 해 지금까지 이들의 루프처럼이됩니다 감사합니다
graphs that will never be looks so there are never any loops you might think that
당신이 생각 수있는 루프가 결코 그래서 외모 없을 것 그래프
if you use a recurrent neural network that there are loops in there but
당신은 재발 성 신경 네트워크를 사용하는 경우가 있음을 거기에 루프하지만,
there's actually no because what we'll do is we'll take a recurrent neural
우리가 할 거 야하는 것이 있기 때문에 실제로는 더 우리는 재발 성 신경이 걸릴 거 있어요
network and will unfold it through time steps and this will all become there
네트워크 및 시간 단계를 통해 전개되며,이 모두가 될 것입니다
will never be a loop in the photograph copy pasted that small piece or time
사진에 루프가 있음을 붙여 복사 할 수 결코 작은 조각 또는 시간
you'll see that more when we actually get into it but he's always looked so
우리가 실제로 그것으로 얻을 때 당신은 더 많은 것을 볼 수 있습니다하지만 그는 항상보고 있어요
let's look at the implementation of this is actually implemented in practice and
이것의 구현보고의 사실 실제로 구현하자
I think will help make this more concrete as well so we always have these
나는 우리가 항상 이러한 그래서뿐만 아니라이보다 구체적를하는 데 도움이됩니다 생각
graphs graphs these are the best way to think about structuring neural networks
그래프는 이러한 신경 네트워크를 구성에 대해 생각하는 가장 좋은 방법입니다 그래프
and so what we end up with is all these gates there were going to seem a bit but
그래서 우리가 결국 어떻게이 모든 게이트가 약간 보일 거라고하지만,
on top of the gates there something that needs to maintain connectivity structure
연결 구조를 유지할 필요가 무언가 게이트 위에
of the same paragraph what gates are connected to each other and so usually
같은 단락의 내용 게이트 그래서 일반적으로 서로 연결되어
that's handled by a graph or object usually in that the net object has needs
그 그래프에 의해 처리 또는 순 객체가 필요가 있는지에 일반적으로 객체의
two main pieces which was the forward and backward peace and this is just you
두 가지 주요 부분 전후 평화이었고, 이것은 당신은 단지 인
two coats run but basically roughly the idea is that in the forward pass
이 코트는 실행되지만 기본적으로 거의 생각은 앞으로 패스이다
trading overall the gates in the circuit that and they're sorted in topological
전체 그들이 위상으로 정렬하는 회로의 게이트를 거래
order what that means is that all the inputs must come to every note before
그게 무슨 뜻인지 주문하면 모든 입력이되기 전에 모든 노트에 와서해야한다는 것입니다
the opportunity consumed just ordered from left to right and we're just
기회는 바로 왼쪽에서 오른쪽으로 주문하고 우리는 그냥있어 소모 된
boarding will call ya forward on every single gate along the way so we iterate
탑승 우리가 반복 그래서 길을 따라 모든 단일 게이트 앞으로 나중에 호출
over that graph and just go forward to every single piece and this object will
이 그래프를 통해 단지 하나 하나 조각 전진이 오브젝트 것
just make sure that happens in the proper connectivity pattern and backward
단지 있는지 확인하는 적절한 연결 패턴과 이전 버전에서 발생
pass we're going in the exact reverse order and we're calling backward on
우리는 정확한 역순으로거야 우리가 역에 전화하는거야 통과
every single gate and these gates will end up communicating gradients to each
모든 단일 게이트 및이 게이트는 각각 그라디언트를 전달 끝날 것
other and the old get changeup and computing the analytic gradients it back
다른 및 이전 가져 오기 체인지업과 분석 그라디언트 그것을 다시 계산
so really an object is a very thin wrapper around all these gates or as we
그래서 진짜 목적은 모든 게이트 주위에 또는 매우 얇은 래퍼는 우리
will see their cold layers layers or gates I'm going to use interchangeably
자신의 차가운 레이어 층 또는 게이트 내가 같은 의미로 사용하는거야 볼 수 있습니다
and they're just very thin wrapper surround connectivity structure of these
그들은이 단지 매우 얇은 래퍼 서라운드 연결 구조있어
gates and calling a forward and backward function on them and then let's look at
게이트는 그들에 순방향 및 역방향 함수를 호출 한 다음의가 살펴 보자
a specific example of one of the gates and how this might be implemented and
게이트의 한 방법이 구현 될 수 있으며의 구체적인 예
this is not just a year ago this is actually more like correct
이것은이 올바른처럼 실제로 더 만 년 전 아닙니다
implementation something like this might run
이 같은 구현 뭔가를 실행할 수 있습니다
at the end so let us enter and multiply gate and how it could be implemented and
마지막에 그래서 우리가 입력 게이트를 곱하자 어떻게 구현 될 수 있으며,
multiply gate in this case is just a binary multiplies receives two inputs
이 경우 다중 게이트 단지 이진 곱셈은 두 개의 입력을 수신
X&Y it computes their multiplication that his ex times why and returns and
X & Y가 자신의 곱셈을 계산 그의 전 시간 왜 반환 및
all these games must be satisfied the API of a forward and backward cool how
모든 게임은 앞으로 얼마나 멋진 이전 버전의 API를 만족해야합니다
do you behave in a forward pass and how they behave in a backward pass and
당신이 앞으로 패스 행동과 그들이 뒤로 패스에서 어떻게 행동하는지 않고
repass just computer whatever in a backward pass we eventually end up
후방 패스에서 우리는 결국 결국 어떤 repass은 컴퓨터
learning about what is our gradient on the final loss to the old ideas as what
것과 오래된 아이디어를 최종 손실에 대한 우리의 기울기를 무엇인지에 대한 학습
we learn that's represented in this variable these head and right now
우리는 지금이 변수에이 머리를 표현하고있어 학습
everything is scalars so X Y is that our numbers here he said is also a number
모든 XY 여기에 우리의 숫자는 그가 말했다 그래서 스칼라입니다 또한 숫자입니다
telling the employers and what this gate is charged in this backward pass is
고용주 어떤이 문이 뒤로 패스에 충전된다 이야기
performing the little piece of general so what we have to compute is how do you
그래서 우리는 무엇을 계산하기 위해 일반의 작은 조각을 수행하면 작업을 수행하는 방법이다
change this gradient these into your inputs X&Y compute the ex NDY and we
전을 계산하여 입력 X에이 그라데이션이 변경 & Y NDY 우리
turned us into backward pass and then the competition on draft will make sure
뒤로 패스로 우리를 설정 한 다음 초안에 경쟁이 있는지 확인합니다
that these get routed properly to all the other bags and if there are any
이러한 것이 다른 모든 백 제대로 전달 얻을 어떤가 있는지
badges that add up the competition grab my dad might add all the ingredients
경쟁을 추가 배지 내 아버지가 모든 재료를 추가 할 수 있습니다 잡아
together ok so how would we implement the DAX and devices for example what is
함께 확인 그래서 우리가 어떻게 무엇 인 예를 들어 DAX와 장치를 구현하는 것
the X in this case it would be equal to the implementation
이 경우 X는 그 구현에 동등한 것
why times easy break and a white and easy additional point to make here by
왜 항상 쉬운 휴식에 의해 여기에 만들 수있는 흰색과 쉽게 추가 점
the way that I added some lies in the past we have to remember these values of
I는 과거에 어떤 거짓말을 첨가하는 방법, 우리는 이들 값을 기억해야
X&Y because we end up using them in a backward pass from assigning them to a
X & Y는 우리가에 할당에서 뒤로 패스를 사용하게하기 때문에
sell stop because I need to remember what X Y are because I need access to
나는에 대한 액세스를 필요로하기 때문에 XY가 기억해야하기 때문에 중지 판매
them in my back yard pass in general and back-propagation when we build these
일반 및 역 전파에 내 뒤뜰 단계의 그들을 우리는 이러한 구축
when you actually the forward pass every single gate must remember the impetus in
실제로 앞으로이 통과 할 때마다 하나의 게이트에 자극을 기억해야한다
any kind of intermediate calculations performed that it needs to do that needs
중간 계산의 종류는 필요하다고 할 필요가 있음을 수행
access to a backward pass so basically we end up running these networks at
후방 패스에 액세스 그래서 기본적으로 우리는 이들 네트워크를 실행 끝
runtime just always keep in mind that as you're doing this forward pass a huge
런타임은 항상 당신이하고있는 것처럼 앞으로 거대한를 통과 있음을 알아 두셔야
amount of stuff gets cashed in your memory and that all has to stick around
물건의 금액은 메모리에 현금화되는 모든가 가지고있는 곁에
because during the propagation and I need access to some of those variables
나는 그 변수의 일부에 대한 액세스를 필요로하는 전파 동안 때문에
and so your memory and the ballooning up during a forward pass backward pass it
그래서 당신의 기억과 앞으로 패스 동안 열기구까지 뒤로 건네
gets all consumed and we need all those intermediaries to actually compete the
모든 소비 얻고 우리는 실제로 경쟁하는 모든 중개인이 필요
proper backward class so that you can get rid of many of these things and you
이러한 것들과 많은 제거 할 수 있도록 적절한 뒤로 클래스
don't have to compete in going to cash them so you can save on memory for sure
당신은 확실히 메모리에 저장할 수 있도록 그들을 현금하려고 경쟁 할 필요가 없습니다
but I don't think most implementations actually worried about that I don't
하지만 난하지 않습니다에 대한 사실 걱정 대부분의 구현을 생각하지 않는다
think there's a lot of logic that deals with that usually end up remembering it
보통 기억 결국 그 다루는 로직이 많이 있다고 생각
anyway I yes I think if you're in an embedded device for example and you were
어쨌든 당신은 예를 들어 임베디드 장치에 있다면 나는 네 생각하고 있었다
eerily by the American strains this is something that you might take advantage
미국 균주에 의해 무시 무시 이것은 당신이 활용할 수있는 무언가이다
of it we know that a neural network only has to run and test time then you might
그것을 우리는 신경 네트워크는 다음 테스트 시간을 당신이 있습니다 실행하는 것을 알고
want to make sure going to the code to make sure nothing gets cashed in case
확인이 없는지 확인하기 위해 코드에 갈 수 있도록 할 경우에 현금으로 도착
you wanna do a backward pass questions yes we remember the local gradients in
당신은 우리가 지방 그라디언트를 기억 예 후방 패스 질문을 할 싶어
the forward pass then we don't have to remember the other intermediates I think
전진 패스는 우리는 내가 생각하는 다른 중간체를 기억할 필요가 없습니다
that might only be the case in such in some simple expressions like this 1 I'm
그는 난이 1 등 몇 가지 간단한 표현에서 이러한 경우를 수 있습니다
not actually sure that's true in general but I mean you're in charge of remember
실제로 있는지 즉, 일반적으로 사실 만 기억 당신이 담당하고있어 의미
whatever you need to perform the backward pass gate by game basis you
당신은 게임으로 당신에 의해 후방 패스 게이트를 수행 할 필요가 무엇
don't know if you can remember whatever you feel like it has a footprint on
당신이에 발자국이 좋아 기분이 어떤 기억 할 수 있는지 모르겠어요
someone and you can be clever with that guy's example of what it looks like in
사람과 당신은의 모습의 그 사람의 예와 영리한 될 수 있습니다
practice we're going to look at specific examples and torture tortures a deep
실제로 우리는 구체적인 예를 살펴거야 고문 깊은 고문
learning framework which we might be going to a bit near the end of the class
우리는 클래스의 끝 부분에 약간에 갈 수있는 학습 프레임 워크
that some of you might end up using for your projects going to the github repo
여러분 중 일부는 github에의 REPO에가는 프로젝트에 사용 끝날 수도
for porridge and you look at the musically it's just a giant collection
와 죽 당신은 음악적으로 그냥 거대한 컬렉션이야 봐
of these later objects and these are the gates gates the same thing so there's
거기 그래서 이러한 나중에 개체의 이러한 게이트 게이트 같은 일이다
all these layers that's really what a deep learning framework is this just a
깊은 학습 프레임 워크는이 단지를 무엇인지 정말 모든 층
whole bunch of layers and a very thin competition graph thing that keeps track
층의 전체 무리를 추적 매우 얇은 경쟁 그래프 일
of all the connectivity and so really the image to have in mind at all these
모든 연결 및 그래서 정말 이미지의 모든에서 염두에두고하는
things are your leg blocks and then we're building up these graphs out of
일이 당신의 다리 블록이며, 우리는 밖으로 이러한 그래프를 구축하고
your league in blocks out of the layers you're putting them together in various
블록에서 리그 층에서 당신은 다양한에서 함께 그들을 가하고있어
ways depending on what you want to achieve and the end up building all
방법은 당신이 달성하려는 작업에 따라와 말까지 모든 건물
kinds of stuff so that's how you work with their own networks so every library
물건의 종류 그래서 당신이 그렇게 자신의 네트워크에있는 모든 라이브러리와 함께 작동 방법
just a whole set of layers that you might want to compute and every layer is
당신이 할 수 있습니다 층의 단지 전체 집합을 계산하고 모든 층이다
implementing a smoky function peace and that function keys knows how to move
연기 함수 평화를 구현하고 그 기능 키를 이동하는 방법을 알고
forward and knows how to do a backward so just above a specific example let's
앞으로 그래서 그냥하자 구체적인 예 위의 이전 버전을 수행하는 방법을 알고
look at the mall constant layer and torch the mall constant layer or chrome
쇼핑몰 상수 층 토치 쇼핑몰 상수 층 또는 크롬 봐
just a scaling by scalar so it takes some tenser X so this is not a scalar
스칼라로 불과 스케일링은 일부 tenser X를 취하도록 그래서이 스칼라 아니다
but it's actually like an array of numbers basically because when we
하지만 숫자의 배열 기본적으로 우리를하기 때문에 같은 사실입니다
actually work with these we do a lot of extras operation so we receive a tensor
실제로 우리가 우리가 텐서를 엑스트라 작업을 많이 받는가이 작업
which is really just and dimensional array and was killed by constant and you
이는 정말하고 차원 배열이며, 일정 및 의해 살해되었다
can see that this actually just a sporty lines there some initialization stuff
이이 실제로 단지 스포티 한 라인 일부 초기화 물건 것을 알 수 있습니다
this is lula by the way if this is looking some foreign to you but there's
이것은이 당신에게 외국을 찾고 있지만, 거기 경우 그런데 룰라입니다
initialisation where you actually passing that a that you want to use as
당신이 실제로 당신이 원하는 그 A가로 사용할 것을 전달 초기화
you are scaling and then during the forward pass which they call update out
당신은 그들이 밖으로 업데이트를 호출 전진 패스 동안 다음 확장되고,
but in a forward pass all they do is they just multiply X and returned it and
하지만 앞으로 패스에 그들이 모두 그들은 단지 X를 곱 그것을 반환하고
into backward pass which they call update grad input there's any statement
그들은 업데이트 대학원 입력 전화를 뒤로 패스에있는 문이있다
here but really when you look at these three live their most important you can
당신이이 세 가지를 볼 때 여기에 있지만 정말 가장 중요한 생활을 수행 할 수 있습니다
see that all is doing its copying into a variable grad
모든 변수 대학원으로의 복사를하고있는 것을 볼 수
would need to compute that's your grade in that you're passing up the great
그 점에서 당신이 훌륭한을 통과하는 성적이다 계산해야
impetus you're copping out but ran up to this your your gradient on final loss
자극 아웃 참을 수가 만하는 것은 최종 손실에이에 그라디언트를 실행
you're copping that over into grad input and you're multiplying by the by the
당신은 대학원 입력에 그 이상 참을 수가있어 당신은에 의해 곱있어
scalar which is what you should be doing because you are your local ratings just
이는 스칼라는 해당 지역의 평점은 그냥 있기 때문에 당신이 일을해야 무엇인가
a and C you take the out but you have to take the gradient from above and just
A와 C는 아웃을하지만 당신은에서 위의 단지 그라데이션을해야
killed by AP which is what these three lines are doing and that's your grad
AP에 의해 살해 이러한 세 가지 라인이 일을하고 당신의 대학원 무엇 인
important that's what you return so that's one of the hundreds of layers
중요한 그것은 당신이 그렇게 그 층의 수백 중 하나 반환 무엇
that are and torture you can also look at examples in cafe get there is also a
그 그리고 당신은 또한 카페에서 예를 볼 수 있습니다 고문은 또한이받을
deep learning framework specifically for images might be working with again if
특히 이미지에 대한 깊은 학습 프레임 워크는 다시 경우 작업 할 수 있습니다
you go into the layers director just see all these layers all of them implement
당신은 모든 층이 모두 구현하는 참조 레이어 디렉터로 이동
the forward backward API so just to give you an example there's a single layer
앞으로 뒤로 API 그래서 그냥 단층 거기에 당신에게 예를 제공합니다
layer takes a blob so comfy likes to call these tensors blogs so it takes a
그것은 소요 있도록 층이 텐서의 블로그를 호출 할 수 있도록 편안 좋아하는 블롭 소요
blob is just an international array of numbers and it passes
덩어리는 숫자에 불과 국제 배열이며 전달
element wise to a single function and so its computing in a forward pass a
하나의 함수에 현명하고 그래서 전방에서의 컴퓨팅가 전달 요소
sigmoid which you can see their use my printer so they're calling it a lot of
그들이 많은 전화하는거야, 그래서 당신이 볼 수 시그 모이 자신의 프린터를 사용
this stuff is just boilerplate getting pointers to all the data and then we
이 물건은 다음 모든 데이터에 대한 포인터를 받고 보일러되어 우리
have a bottom blob and we're calling a sigmoid function on the bottom and
하부 블롭이 우리는 아래의 시그 모이 드 함수를 호출하고 있고
that's just a sigmoid function right there that's why we compute in a
우리가에 계산하는 이유는 그건 바로 거기에 그냥 시그 모이 드 함수의
backward pass some boilerplate stuff but really what's important is we need to
이전 버전과 일부 상용구 물건을 전달하지만 정말 중요한 것은 우리가 필요하다
compute the gradient times the chain rule here so that's what you see in this
즉이에 무엇을보고, 그래서 그라데이션 시간을 여기에 체인 규칙을 계산
line that's where the magic happens when we take the
우리가 걸릴 때 마법 발생의 라인
so they call the greetings dips and you compute the bottom diff is the top if
그래서 그들은 인사 강하를 호출하면 하단 DIFF 상단 경우입니다 계산
times this piece which is really the that's the local gradient so this is
시간이 그래서 정말 그 지역 그라데이션의 인이 작품
chain rule happening right here through that multiplication so and so every
그래서 그래서 모든 것을 곱셈을 통해 바로 여기 일어나고 체인 규칙
single layer just a forward backward API and then you have a competition growth
다음 단일 층 단지 앞뒤로 API 당신은 경쟁 성장을
on top or another object that troubled connectivity and questions about some of
상단 또는 일부에 대한 연결 및 질문에 고민 또 다른 목적에
these implementations and so on
이러한 구현 등
because when you want to do right away to a backward and I have a gradient and
당신이 바로 후방에 수행 할 때 나는 그라데이션을 가지고 있기 때문에
I can do an update right up my alley gradient and I change my way it's a tiny
그것은 작은이야 내가 바로 내 골목 그라데이션까지 업데이트를 할 수있는 나는 내 방식을 변경
bit and the direction the negative direction of your writing so overcome
비트와 당신의 쓰기의 음의 방향이 그렇게 극복 방향
the loss backward computer gradient and then the update uses the gradient to
손실 이전 버전과 컴퓨터 그라데이션 및 다음 업데이트는 그라디언트를 사용
increment you are a bit so that's what keeps happening Lupin III neural network
그 일이 일어나고 루팡 III의 신경 네트워크를 유지 무엇​​ 때문에 당신이 조금 있습니다 증가
that's all that's happening forward backward update forward backward state
그 앞으로 뒤로 업데이트를 앞뒤로 상태를 일어나는 모든이다
will see that you're asking about the for loop therefore Lapeer I do notice ok
이 때문에 루프 LAPEER의에 대해 문의하는 것을 볼 수 있습니다 내가 확인 통지 할
yeah they have a for loop yes you'd like us to be better eyes and that actually
그래 그들은 루프 그래 당신은 더 나은 눈으로 우리를 싶은 있고 실제로
sure this is C++ so I think they just go for it
확인이 그래서 그들은 그냥 갈 생각 ++ C이다
yeah so this is a CPU implementation by the way I should mention that this is a
그래 그래서 이것은 내가이는 것을 언급해야하는 방식에 의해 CPU의 구현입니다
CPU implementation of a similar there's a second file that implement the
비슷한의 CPU 구현은 구현 번째 파일을 거기에
simulator on GPU and that's correct code and so that's a separate file its
GPU에 시뮬레이터와 그 올바른 코드이고 그래서 별도의 파일입니다 그
would-be sigmoid out see you or something like that I'm not showing you
시그 모이-것 밖으로 그런 당신이나 무언가가 당신을 보여주는 아니에요 참조
that the russians ok great so I like to make is will be of course working with
확인 위대한 러시아가 내가 할 좋아하는 것은 작업 과정이 될 것입니다
better so these things flowing along our grass are not just killers they're going
더 나은 그래서 우리의 잔디 따라 흐르는 이런 일들은거야 그냥 살인자 없습니다
to be entire back to us and so nothing changes the only thing that is different
우리에게 다시 전체 수 그래서 아무것도 다른 유일한 변화 없습니다
now since these are vectors XY and Z are vectors is that these local gradient
이제이 때문에 벡터 XY 및 Z는 벡터입니다되어있는이 지역의 그라데이션이
which before used to be just a scalar now there in general for general
전에 일반의 일반적인 지금이 바로 스칼라로 사용하는
expressions their full Jacobian matrices and so it could be a major exodus
자신의 모든 코비안 행렬을 표현하고 그래서 주요 출 수
two-dimensional matrix and basically tells me what is the influence of every
매트릭스 2 차원 기본적으로 모든의 영향이 무엇인지 알려줍니다
single element in X on every single element of
모든 단일 요소에 X에서 하나의 요소
and that's what you can be a major source and the gradient the same
그것은 당신이 주요 소스와 그라데이션 동일 할 수있는 작업
expression as before but now they hear the IDX is a vector and DL Moody said is
그들은 IDX는 벡터이다 듣고 DL 무디 전에 그러나 지금과 같은 식입니다 말했다
designed as an actor and designed by Dax is an entire Jacobian matrix end up with
배우로 설계 닥스에 의해 디자인하는 것은 전체 코비안 행렬로 끝날 것입니다
an entire matrix-vector multiply to actually change the gradient know so
실제로 그라데이션을 변경하려면 전체 행렬 - 벡터 곱셈 그렇게 알고
I'll come back to this point in a bit you never actually end up forming the
난 당신이 실제로 형성 결국 결코 조금의이 시점에 다시 올 것이다
Jacobian you'll never actually do this matrix multiply most of the time this is
코비 실제로이 행렬은 대부분의 시간이된다 번식 할 수 없을거야
just a general way of looking at you know arbitrary function and I need to
당신을 찾고 그냥 일반적인 방법은 임의의 기능을 알고 난 필요
keep track of this and I think that these two are actually out of order
이 추적하고 나는이 두 가지 순서가 실제로 생각
because he said by the exit the Jacobian which should be on the left side so
그는 왼쪽에 있어야 출구 코비안 말했다 때문에 이렇게
that's that's a mistaken slide because it should be a major factor multiplied
그게 중요한 요인이 곱해야하기 때문에 그가 잘못 슬라이드의의
so I'll show you why you don't actually need to perform those Jacobins so let's
당신이 실제로 그렇게하자 그 자코뱅를 수행 할 필요가 없습니다 왜 그렇게 당신을 보여 드리죠
work with a specific example that is relatively common in the works
작품 비교적 일반적인 구체 예에서 작동
suppose we have this nonlinearity max 50 index so really what this is operation
우리가 정말이 동작이 무엇인지이 비선형 최대 50 인덱스가 있다고 가정
is doing its receiving a vector sale 4096 numbers which is a typical thing
그 전형적인 것 인 4096 번호 벡터 판매를 수신하고있다
you might want to do
당신이 수행 할 수 있습니다
4096 numbers real value
4096 번호 진정한 가치
and your computing an element wise threshold 0 so anything that is lower
당신은 요소 현명한 임계 값을 낮은 0 그래서 아무것도 계산
than 0 gets clamped 20 and that's your function that your computing and sew up
0 20 고정됩니다 그것은 당신의 컴퓨팅 함수의 최대 바느질보다
the victories on the same dimension to the question here I'd like to ask is
질문에 동일한 차원의 승리는 여기에 내가 물어 싶습니다
what is the size of the Jacobian matrix for this layer 4096 4096 in principle
원칙적으로이 계층 4096 4096에 대한 자 코비안 행렬의 크기는 무엇인가
every single number in here could have influenced every single number in there
여기에있는 모든 단일 번호는 거기에 매 수에 영향을 수 있었다
but that's not the case necessarily right to the second question is so this
하지만 두 번째 질문에 반드시 오른쪽의 경우는 그래서이됩니다 아니다
is a huge measure sixteen million numbers but why would you never formed
거대한 측정 천육백만 수 있지만, 당신은 왜 형성되지 않을 것입니다
what does actually look like always be matrix because every one of these 4096
실제로 무엇을 항상 같이 행렬 않기 때문에 이러한 4096의 모든 일
could have influenced every it is so the communists still a giant 4085 4086
그것은 거대한 4085 4086 여전히 공산주의자를 모든입니다 영향을 수 있었다
matrix but has special structure right and what is that special structure but
매트릭스 그러나 특수 구조의 권리가 무엇이며 특별한 구조 만
so is a huge tits 4095 4096 matrix but there's only elements on the diagonal
그래서 큰 가슴 4095 4096 행렬 만 요소는 대각선에있다
because this is an element was operation and moreover they're not just once but
이 요소가 작동했다이며, 또한 그들은 단지 한 번하지 않은 있기 때문에
whichever element was less than zero it was clamped 20 so some of these ones
어느 요소가 그래서 이러한 것들 중 일부를 20 제로보다 고정 하였다
actually are zeros in whichever elements had a lower than zero value during the
실제로 요소가 동안보다 낮은 제로 값을 가지고 중의 제로입니다
forward pass and so the Jacobian would just be almost no identity matrix but
앞으로 전달하고 그래서 코비안 그냥 거의 행렬 없을 것입니다하지만,
some of them are actually Sarah so you never actually would want to form the
당신이 결코 실제로을 형성 할 것이다, 그래서 그들 중 일부는 실제로 사라입니다
full Jacobean because that's silly and so you never actually want to carry out
전체 코빈 그 바보 그래서 당신은 실제로 수행 싶지 않기 때문에
this operation as a matrix-vector multiply because their special structure
그들의 특별한 구조 때문에 매트릭스 - 벡터 곱셈 연산 등이
that we want to take advantage of and so in particular the gradient the backward
우리의 등 특정 기울기 후방을에 활용하려는
pass for this operation is very very easy because you just want to look at
그냥보고 싶지 때문에 아주 아주 쉽게이 작업에 전달
all the dimensions where your input was less than zero and you want to kill the
귀하의 의견은 당신이 죽이고 싶어 제로보다 작은이었다 모든 차원
gradient and those mentioned you want to set the gradient 20 in those dimensions
그라데이션과 언급은 그 차원에서 그라데이션 (20)을 설정하려면
so you take the grid out but here and whichever numbers were less than zero
그래서 당신은 밖으로 그러나 여기 그리드를 가지고 있었다 중 번호 제로보다 작은
just set them 200 and then you can ask
그냥 200을 설정 한 다음 당신은 요청할 수 있습니다
so very simple operations in the in the end in terms of
측면에서 결국에 이렇게 아주 간단한 작업
if you want to you can do that but that's internal to you and said the gate
당신은 할 수 있습니다 당신이 원하는하지만 당신 내부의 게이트 말했다 경우
and you can use that to do backdrop but what's going back to other dates they
당신은 배경을 수행하는 것을 사용할 수 있지만 다른 날짜로 다시 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지 그들
only care about the gradient vector so we'll never actually run into that case
그라데이션 벡터 걱정 만 그래서 우리는 실제로 그런 경우에 실행하지 않을거야
because we almost always have a single out but skill and rallied in the end
우리는 거의 항상 하나의 아웃하지만 기술을 가지고 결국 재편성하기 때문에
because we're interested in Los functions so we just have a single
우리는 로스 기능에 관심이 있기 때문에 우리는 단지 하나가
number at the end that were interested in trading for prospective if we had
우리가 있던 경우에 장래에 대한 거래에 관심이 끝 번호
multiple outputs then we have to keep track of all of those as well
다중 출력 후 우리는 그 모두의도를 추적 할 수 있습니다
imperil when we do the backpropagation but we just have to get a rally loss
우리는 역 전파 할 때 위태롭게하지만 우리는 집회 손실을 얻을 수있다
function so as not to worry about that so I want to also make the point that
기능 그래서 나는 또한 지점을 확인하려면 그것에 대해 걱정하지 않도록 그
actually four thousand crazy usually we use many batches so say many batch of a
실제로 사천 미친 일반적으로 우리가 사용하는 많은 일괄 처리하므로 여러 배치를 말한다
hundred elements going through the same time and then you end up with a hundred
백 요소는 같은 시간을 통과하고 당신은 백으로 끝날
4096 emotional factors that are all coming in peril but all the examples
4096 감정적 모든 위험에서 오는 요인하지만 모든 예제
enemy better processed independently of each other in peril and so that you
적을 더 위험에서 서로 독립적으로 처리하므로 그
could really end up being four hundred million so huge so you never formally is
정말 당신이 공식적으로하지 않을 수 있도록 사억이 너무 큰 것을 끝낼 수 있었다
basically and you takes to take care to actually take advantage of the sparsity
기본적으로 당신은 실제로 희소성을 활용하는데주의를 기울여야하는 데 걸리는
structure in the Jacobian and you hand code operations you don't actually right
코비안과 손 코드 작업에서 구조 당신은 실제로 바로하지 않습니다
before the generalized general inside any gate implementation ok so I'd like
모든 게이트 구현 내부의 일반화 된 일반적인하기 전에 확인 그래서 내가 좋아하는 것
to point out that your assignment he'll be writing as Max and so on and I just
과제 그가 최대로 작성하는 등 단지 I됩니다 지적합니다
wanted to give you a hint on the design of how you actually should approach this
실제로이 접근 방법의 디자인에 당신에게 힌트를주고 싶어
problem what you should do is just think about it as a back propagation even if
당신이 무엇을해야하는지 문제는 다시 전파에도 것처럼 생각된다
you're doing this for classification optimization so roughly or structure
당신은 분류 최적화 너무 약하거나 구조에 대해이 작업을하고있는
should look something like this where against major computation and units that
주요 계산 및 단위에 대해이 곳처럼 보일 것이다 그
you know the local gradient off and then do backdrop when you actually these
당신은 떨어져 지역의 기울기를 알고 다음 배경 당신 실제로 이러한 작업을 수행
gradients in your assignment so in the top your code will look something like
과제에 그라디언트 코드는 같을 것이다 상단에 있도록
this where we don't have any graph structure because you're doing
당신이하고있는 때문에 우리는 어떤 그래프 구조가없는 경우
everything in line so no crazy I just running like that that you have to do
라인의 모든 그래서 미친 난 그냥 당신이해야 할 그 그런 식으로 실행되지
you will do that in a second assignment you'll actually come up with a graphic
당신은 두 번째 과제를 실제로 그래픽을 마련하고 있다고 할 것입니다
object you implement your layers but my first assignment you're just doing it in
당신이 당신의 레이어를 구현하지만 내 첫 임무는 바로 그것을하고있는 객체
line just straight up an awesome and so complete your scores based on wnx
라인은 똑바로 굉장한 등 wnx에 따라 점수를 완료
compute these margins which are Maxim 0 and the score differences compute the
맥심 0있는 이러한 여백을 계산하고 점수 차이는를 계산
loss and then do backdrop and in particular I would really advise you to
다음 손실 및 배경을 특히 나는 정말로 당신을 권합니다
have this intermediate course let you create a matrix and then compute the
이 중간 과정은 당신이 매트릭스를 만들 수있는 다음을 계산
gradient on scores before you can view the gradient on your weights and so
당신의 무게 등은 그라데이션을 볼 수 있습니다 전에 점수에 그라데이션
chain chain rule here like you might be tempted to try to just arrived W the
여기에 당신과 같은 체인 체인 규칙은 단지 (W) 도착하려고하는 유혹 될 수 있습니다
gradient on W equals and then implement that and that's an unhealthy way of
W 등호에 그라데이션과 그 구현과 그의 건강에 해로운 방법
approaching problem so state your competition and do backdrop through this
문제를 접근하는 것은 그래서 당신의 경쟁을 명시하고이를 통해 배경을
course and they will help you out so
물론 그들은 당신을 너무 밖으로 도움이 될 것입니다
so far are hopelessly large so we end up in this competition structures and these
지금까지 우리는이 경쟁 구조와 이들에 절망적으로 큰 끝날된다
intermediate nodes forward backward API for both the notes and also for the
중간은 대한주의 사항도 모두 앞으로 뒤로 API 노드
graph structure and infrastructure is usually a very thin wrapper on all these
그래프 구조와 하부 구조는 일반적으로 모든 이들의 매우 얇은 래퍼입니다
layers and it can handle the communication between him and his
층과 그 사이의 통신을 처리 할 수​​있는 그의
communication is always along like doctors being passed around in practice
통신은 따라 의사가 실제로 주위에 전달되는 것처럼 항상
when we write these implementations what we're passing around our DS and
우리는 우리가 우리의 DS 주위를 통과하는지 이러한 구현을 쓸 때와
dimensional sensors really what that means is just an end dimensional array
차원 센서는 정말 무슨 뜻인지 그냥 끝 차원 배열입니다
array those are what goes between the gates and then internally every single
이러한 배열은 무슨 일이 내부적으로 다음 게이트 사이에 매일 진행됩니다
gate knows what to do in the forward and backward pass ok so at this point I'm
게이트는 확인을 전후 패스에 무엇을 알고 난이 시점에서 이렇게
going to end with that propagation and I'm going to go into neural networks so
그 전파로 끝나는 것 나는 그렇게 신경 네트워크에 갈거야
any questions before we move on from background
우리는 배경에서 이동하기 전에 모든 질문
operation challenging assignment almost is how do you make sure that you do all
동작 도전 과제는 거의 방법이 모든 수행해야합니다 않습니다이다
the sufficiently nicely with operations in numpy so that's going to be something
충분히 잘 NumPy와의 작업과 그 뭔가 될 것 있도록
that brings our stuff that you guys are going to be like and what you want them
그것은 우리 너희들처럼 될 예정 물건과 당신이 그들을 원하는을 제공합니다
to be I don't think he'd want to do that
수 나는 그가 그렇게 할 거라고 생각하지 않습니다
yeah I'm not sure maybe that works but it's up to you to design this and to
그래, 나는 아마 작동이 확실하지 않다하지만이과에 디자인까지 당신의
back up through it so that's that's what we're going to go to neural networks is
다시 그것을 통해 그, 그래서 그것은 우리가 신경망에 갈거야 무슨이다
exactly what they look like you'll be involving me and this is what happens
정확히 당신이 날을 포함 할 것처럼 보이는 이것은 무슨 일이 무엇인지
when you search on Google Images networks this is I think the first
당신이 Google 이미지 네트워크에서 검색 할 때이 내가 처음 생각입니다
result of something like that so let's look at the networks and before we dive
이 같은 결과는 그래서는 네트워크를보고 우리가 다이빙을하기 전에하자
into neural networks actually I'd like to do it first without all the brain
신경 네트워크에 실제로 나는 모든 뇌없이 먼저 수행하고 싶습니다
stuff so forget that their neural forget that they have any relation whatsoever
물건 그래서 그들의 신경은 그들이 어떤 관계든지를 잊지 잊지
to brain they don't forget if you thought that they did but they do let's
뇌에 그들은 당신이 그들이했던 것을 생각하면 잊지 마세요하지만 그들은하자 할
just look at school functions well before we thought that equals WX is what
그냥이 WX 무엇입니까 동일 우리가 생각도하기 전에 학교 기능을보고
we've been working with so far but now as I said we're going to start to make
나는 우리가 만드는 시작하는거야 말했듯이 우리는 지금까지하지만 지금은 작업했습니다
that F more complex and so if you want to use a neural network then you're
F 더 복잡하고 그래서 당신은 당신이있어 신경 네트워크를 사용하려는 경우
going to change that equation to this so this is a two-layer neural network and
그래서이 이것에 해당 방정식을 변경하려고하는 것은 두 계층 신경망이며,
that's what it looks like and it's just a more complex mathematical expression X
그게처럼 보이는 그것은 단지 더 복잡한 수학 식 X의 무엇을
and so what's happening here as you receive your input X and you make
당신이 당신의 입력 X를 받고 당신이 만드는으로 그래서 무슨 일이 일어나고
multiplied by matrix just like we did before
우리가 전에했던 것처럼 매트릭스를 곱한
now what's coming next what comes next is a nonlinearity or activation function
지금 무엇을 다음에 오는 것을 옆오고하는 것은 비선형 또는 활성화 기능입니다
I'm going to go into several choices that you might make for these in this
나는 당신이 이들에 대해 할 수있는 몇 가지 선택에 갈거야
case I'm using the threshold 0 as an activation function so basically we're
케이스는 정말 기본적으로 우리가있어 활성화 함수로 임계 값 0을 사용하고 있습니다
doing matrix multiply we threshold everything they get 20 and then we do
행렬 곱셈 우리 임계 모든 일을 그들은 20 얻을하고 우리가 할
one more major supply and that gives us are scarce and so if I was to drop this
또 하나의 주요 공급하고 우리에게주는이 부족하다 그래서 난이 드롭 인 경우
say in case of C for 10 with three South 3072 numbers going in the pixel values
세 남아 3072 참조 화소 값을가는 10 C의 경우라고
and before we just went one single major metabolite discourse we went right away
우리가 하나의 주요 대사 산물 담론을 가기 전에 우리는 바로 갔다
numbers but now we get to go through this intermediate representation
(22)
pendants hidden state will call them hidden layers so each of hundred-numbers
상태 숨겨진 펜던트 그래서 숨겨진 레이어 백 - 각 숫자를 그들에게 전화한다
or whatever you want your size of the network to be so this is a high pressure
또는 당신이되고 네트워크의 사이즈를 원하는 그래서 이것은 높은 압력
that's a a hundred and we go through this intermediate representation so make
그 AA 백 그리고 우리는 그렇게 할이 중간 표현을 통해 이동
sure to multiply gives us hundred-numbers threshold at zero and
곱해야 제로에서 우리에게 백 번호 임계 값을 제공하고
then one will make sure that this course and since we have more numbers we have
다음 하나는 확실이이 과정을하고 우리가 더 많은 숫자를 가지고 있기 때문에 우리는이
more wiggle to do more interesting things so I'm or one particular example
더 호기심이 난 그래서 더 흥미로운 또는 하나의 특정 예를 수행하는
of something interesting you might want to do what you might think that in the
당신이에서 그런 생각 무엇을 수행 할 수 있습니다 흥미로운의
latter could do is going back to the example of interpreting linear
해석 선형의 예를 다시 것입니다 할 수있는 후자의
classifiers on C part 10 and we saw the car class has this red car that tries to
C 부 (10)에 분류 우리는 자동차 클래스가 시도이 빨간 차를 가지고 보았다
merge all the modes of different car space in different directions and so in
다른 자동차의 모든 공간 모드 상이한 방향 등의 병합
this case one single layer one single leader crossfire had to go across all
이 경우 하나의 층을 하나의 리더 일제 공격 모두를 가로 질러 가야했다
those modes and we couldn't deal with for example of different colors that
이러한 모드와 우리는 서로 다른 색상의 예를 들어 다루지 수있는
wasn't very natural to do but now we have hundred-numbers in this
할 매우 자연스러운하지 않았다 그러나 지금 우리는이에 백 번호를
intermediate and so you might imagine for example that one of those numbers
중간 그래서 당신은 예를 들어 그 숫자의 한 상상
could be just picking up on the red carpet leasing forward is just gotta
단지 앞으로 임대 레드 카펫에 따기 수 있습니다 단지 돼있다
find is there a wrecked car facing forward another one could be red car
빨간 자동차가 될 수 앞으로 또 다른 하나를 직면 난파 자동차가 발견
facing slightly to the left
왼쪽으로 약간 직면
let carvey seems like the right and those elements of age would only become
하자 carvey 오른쪽처럼 보인다 연령의 이러한 요소는 될 것입니다
positive if they find that thing in the image
긍정적 인 사람들은 이미지의 그 일을 찾을 경우
otherwise they stay at zero and so another age might look for green cards
그렇지 않으면 제로 숙박 등 다른 연령은 녹색 카드를 보일 수 있습니다
or yellow cards or whatever else in different orientations so now we can
노란색 카드 나 이제 서로 다른 방향에서 다른 무엇이든 우리는 할 수 또는
have a template for all these different modes and so these neurons turn on or
이러한 모든 다른 모드에 대한 템플릿을 가지고 있으므로 이러한 뉴런을 켜거나
off if they find the thing they're looking for some specific type and then
그들은 다음 몇 가지 구체적인 유형과 찾고있는 것을 발견하면 해제
this W two major scan some across all those little card templates and I we
모든 작은 카드 템플릿과 나는 우리를 가로 질러이 W 두 가지 주요 검사 일부
have like say twenty card templates of what you look like and now to complete
같은 완료하기 위해 지금 당신이 어떻게 생겼는지의 스물 카드 템플릿을 말하고있다
the scoring classifier there's an additional measures so we have a choice
우리는 선택의 여지가 있도록 점수 분류는 추가 조치를 거기에
of a weighted sum over them and so if anyone of them turned on then through my
그들에 가중 합과 그 사람을 통해 다음 켜져 그렇다면 내
way it's somewhat positive weights presumably I would be adding up and
방법은 다소 긍정적 인 가중치는 아마도 내가 위로하고 추가 할 것입니다
getting a higher score and so now I can have this multimodal our classifier
높은 점수를 얻기 때문에 지금은이 복합 우리의 분류를 가질 수있다
through this additional hidden layer between there and wavy reason for why
이 이유에 대해 물결 모양의 이유와이 부가 숨겨진 계층을 통해
these would do something more interesting
이들은 더 재미있는 일을 할 것입니다
was a question for extra points in the assignment and do something fun or extra
할당에 추가 점수에 대한 질문이었다 뭔가 재미 또는 추가 할
and so you get the carpet whatever you think is interesting experiment and will
그래서 당신은 당신이 흥미있는 실험이 생각과 의지대로 카펫을 얻을
give you some bonus points that's good candidate for for something you might
당신에게 뭔가를 당신이 수도에 대한 좋은 후보의 일부 보너스 포인트를 제공
want to investigate whether that works or not
그 작동 여부를 조사 할
questions
질문
allocated over the different modes of the dataset and I don't have a good
데이터 세트의 다양한 모드를 통해 할당 나는 좋은이 없습니다
answer for that this since we're going to train this fully with
우리는 완전히로이 훈련을거야 때문에 그 이것에 대한 대답
back-propagation
역 전파
I think it's like a naive to think that there will be exact template for sale
나는 판매를위한 정확한 템플릿이있을 것이라고 생각하는 순진한처럼 생각
let carvey seeing red carpet is left you probably want to find that you'll find
레드 카펫을보고 carvey 당신은 아마 당신이 찾을 것을 발견 할 남아 내버려
these kind of like mixes and weird things intermediates and so on
그래서 같은 믹스와 이상한 일 중간체 및 이러한 종류
coming animal optimally find a way to truncate your data with its boundaries
동물을 오는 최적의 경계를 사용하여 데이터를자를 수있는 방법을 찾을
and kuwait's relegated just adjust the company could come alright so it's
쿠웨이트의 그냥 그래서 확실히 올 수있는 회사를 조정 강등
really hard to say well become tangled up I think that's right so that's the
정말 열심히 잘 나는 그이를 그래서 그 잘 생각 휩쓸 리게 될 대답
size of hidden layer and a high primarily get to choose that so I chose
숨겨진 레이어 주로 높은의 크기는 내가 선택한 것을 선택하세요
hundred usually that's going to be usually you'll see that we're going to
백은 일반적으로 그것은 우리가 가고있는 것을 볼 수 있습니다 일반적으로 될 것
this a lot but usually you want them to be as big as possible as its your
이 많이 있지만, 일반적으로 당신은 그들이 당신의 가능한 한 큰되고 싶어
computer and so on so more is better I'm going to that
등 컴퓨터가 그래서 더 나은 내가 그에게 갈거야입니다
asking do we always take max 10 nature and we don't get this like five slides
우리는 항상 최대 10 특성을 가지고 않습니다 물어 우리는 다섯 슬라이드처럼이 얻을하지 않습니다
away somewhere to go into neural networks I guess maybe I should just go
멀리 어딘가에 내가 아마 난 그냥 가야 추측 신경 네트워크로 이동합니다
ahead and take questions near the end if you wanted this to be a three-layer
이는 3 층으로 원한다면 앞서 및 끝 부분에 질문을
neural network by the way there's a very simple way in which we just extend
우리가 확장되는 아주 간단한 방법이 방법에 의해 신경 네트워크
that's right so we just keep continuing the same pattern we have all these
그것은 우리가 단지 우리가 모든이 동일한 패턴을 계속 유지하도록 맞아
intermediate hidden nodes and then we can keep making our network deeper and
중간 노드를 숨겨 후 우리는 우리의 네트워크는 깊은하게 유지할 수 있으며,
deeper and you can compute more interesting functions because you're
깊은 당신이이기 때문에 당신은 더 많은 흥미로운 기능을 계산할 수 있습니다
giving yourself more time to compute something interesting and henry VIII way
자신에게 시간을 더주는 것은 흥미로운과 헨리 VIII의 방법으로 계산하기
up one other slide I want to flash is that training a two-layer neural network
내가 깜빡 할 하나의 다른 슬라이드 달려 그 두 계층 신경망 훈련
I mean it's actually quite simple when it comes down to it so this is like
나는 그렇게이가 내려 오면이 같은 사실은 꽤 간단 의미
borrowed from Blockbuster and basically the price is roughly eleven lines of
의 블록 버스터에서 빌린 기본적으로 가격은 대략 열​​한 라인
Python to implement a two layer neural network during binary classification on
파이썬은 이진 분류 동안 두 계층 신경망을 구현하는
what is this two-dimensional better to have a two dimensional data matrix X you
이 이차원 더 이차원 데이터 행렬 X가 무엇 당신
have thirty three dimensional and you have a binary labels for why and then
서른세 차원이 있고 왜 다음에 대한 이진 레이블이
sin 0 sin 1 are your weight matrices wait one way to end so I think they're
죄 0 죄 (1)는 당신의 체중 행렬 그래서 나는 그들이 있다고 생각 종료 한 가지 방법을 기다릴 수 있습니다
called central synapse but mature and then this is the opposition group here
중앙 시냅스하지만 성숙한라고하며 다음이 반대 그룹은 여기
and what you what you're seeing here I should use my point for more than just
당신은 당신이보고있는 것을 내가 단지보다 더 내 지점을 사용한다
being here as we're completing the first layer activations but and this is using
우리는 첫 번째 계층 활성화를 완료하고 있지만, 이것이 사용되는 여기
a signal nonlinearity not a max of 0 necks and we're going to a bit of what
신호 비선형 0이 아닌 목의 최대 및 우리의 비트에가는하는지
these nonlinearities might be more than one form is reviewing the first layer
이러한 비선형는 하나의 형태 이상이 1 층을 검토 할 수 있습니다
and the second layer and then its computing here right away the backward
두 번째 레이어 바로 여기에 다음의 컴퓨팅 후방 및
pass so this adult adult as the gradient gel to the gradient ml 1 and the
구배 용액 (1)과의 구배 겔 정도로이 성인 성인 합격
gradient and this is a major update here so right away he's doing an update at
그라데이션이 너무 바로 그 업데이트에를하고있어 여기에 주요 업데이트입니다
the same time as during the final piece of backdrop here where he formulated the
그는 공식화 그 다음에 배경의 최종 부분 동안과 같이 동시에
gradient on the W and right away he said adding 22 gradient here and some really
바로 W 및 그라데이션 그는 여기 정말 (22) 경사를 추가했다
eleven lines supplies to train the neural network
열한 라인 공급 신경망을 훈련합니다
classification the reason that this loss may look slightly different from what
이 손실은 무엇과 약간 다를 수 있습니다 이유를 분류
you've seen right now is that this is a logistic regression loss so you saw a
당신은 지금 볼 당신이보고, 그래서 이것은 로지스틱 회귀 손실이 있다는 것
generalization of it which is a nice classifier into multiple dimensions but
여러 차원으로 좋은 분류가 그것의 일반화하지만,
this is basically a logistic loss being updated here and you can go through this
이것은 기본적으로 여기에 업데이트되는 물류 손실이며이 통과 할 수 있습니다
in more detail by yourself but the logistic regression lost look slightly
자신보다 상세하게하지만 잃어버린 로지스틱 회귀가 약간 보일
different and that's being that's inside there but otherwise yes this is not too
다른 그리고 그 안에있다중인 있지만 그렇지 않으면 네이 너무 없습니다
crazy of a competition and very few lines of code suffice actually train
실제로 훈련 코드 충분할의 경쟁 미친 매우 몇 줄
these networks everything else is plus how do you make an official and how do
다른 이들 네트워크의 모든 플러스 방법은 어떻게합니까 공식을 만들어 않습니다
you there's a cross-validation pipeline that you need to have it all this stuff
당신은 당신이 그것을 모든 물건을 가질 필요가 교차 검증 파이프 라인있다
that goes on top to actually give these large code bases but the kernel of it is
즉 그것이 실제로 이러한 큰 코드베이스하지만 커널을 제공하기 위해 상단에 간다
quite simple we compute these layers forward pass backward pass through an
매우 간단 우리는 뒤로 통과 이러한 층이 앞으로 통과 계산
update when it rains but the rain is creating your personal initial random
업데이트는 비가 오면하지만 비는 개인 초기 랜덤를 만드는 것입니다
weights so you need to start somewhere so you generate a random W
당신이 임의의 W를 생성 할 수 있도록 가중치는 그래서 당신은 어딘가에 시작해야
now I want to mention that you'll also be training a two-layer neural network
지금 당신은 또한 두 계층 신경망을 훈련 할 것이다 언급 할
in this class so you'll be doing something very similar to this but
이 클래스에 그래서 당신이 매우 비슷한 일을하고있을거야하지만,
you're not using logistic regression and you might have different activation
당신은 로지스틱 회귀를 사용하지 않는 당신은 다른 활성화가있을 수 있습니다
functions but again just my advice to you when you implement this is staged
기능 그러나 다시이 구현 당신에게 내 조언을 개최한다
your computation into these intermediate results and then do proper
당신이 중간 결과로 계산 한 다음 적절한 수행
backpropagation into every intermediate result so you might have you compute
모든 중간 결과에 역 전파 그래서 당신은 당신이 계산해야 할 수도 있습니다
your computer you receive these weight matrices and also the biases I don't
컴퓨터가 이러한 무게 행렬 또한 편견 그렇게하지를받을
believe you have biases p.m. in your slot max but here you'll have biases so
믿는 당신은 당신의 슬롯 최대의 편견의 오후를 가지고 있지만 여기에 당신은 너무 편견이있을 것이다
take your weight matrices in the biases computer person later computers course
편견 컴퓨터 사람이 나중에 컴퓨터 과정에서 체중 행렬을
complete your loss and then do backward pass so backdrop in this course then
당신의 손실을 완료 한 다음 뒤로 다음이 과정에서 너무 배경을 통과 할
backdrop into the weights at the second layer and backdrop into this h1 doctor
이 H1 의사에 두 번째 레이어와 배경의 무게에 배경
and then through eight-run backdrop into the first weight matrices and spices do
다음을 통해 최초의 무게 매트릭스와 향신료 않습니다에 배경을 팔 실행
proper backpropagation here otherwise if you tried and right away just say what
여기에 적절한 역 전파 그렇지 않으면 시도하면 바로 바로 말
is DWI on what is going on W one if you just try to make it a single expression
당신은 단지 하나의 표현 만들려고하면 어떻게 W 하나를 것입니다에 음주 운전하다
for it will be way too large and headaches so do it through a series of
그것이 너무 클 것이며 대한 두통 정도의 일련 그것을
steps and back-propagation
단계 및 역 전파
that's just a hint
그건 그냥 힌트입니다
ok now I'd like to say that was the presentation of neural networks without
확인 지금은하지 않고 그 신경망의 표현이었다 말을하고 싶습니다
all the bring stuff and it looks fairly simple so now we're going to make it
모든 물건을 가지고, 우리가 그것을 만들거야 그것은 지금 매우 간단 보인다
slightly more insane by folding in all kinds of like motivations mostly
약간 더 미친 같은 동기의 모든 종류의 접이식에 의해 주로
historical about like how this came about that it's related to bring it all
이이 모든 것을 가지고 관련이 있는지에 대해 온 방법 등 역사에 대한
and so we have neural networks and we have neurons inside these neural
그리고 우리는 신경 네트워크를 가지고 우리는 이러한 신경 내의 신경이
networks so this is what I look like just what happens when you search on
이 때문에 네트워크는 내가 당신이 검색 할 때 발생하는 그냥 뭐처럼 보이는 것입니다
image search Iran so there you go now your actual biological neurons don't
이미지 검색이란은 그래서 당신은 이제 실제 생물학적 인 뉴런하지 않는 이동
look like this are currently more like that and so on
같이 더 많은 그래서 그와 같은 현재
just very briefly just to give you an idea about where this is all coming from
그냥 아주 간단하게 단지 모두에서 오는 당신이 어디 이것에 대해 생각을한다주고
you have a cell body or so much like to call it and it's got all these dendrites
당신은 세포체이 있거나 너무 많이 전화를 좋아하고는 모든 수상 돌기를 가지고
that are connected to other neurons there's a cluster of other neurons and
다른 뉴런에 연결되어있는 다른 뉴런의 클러스터가 그리고
somebody's over here and then drives are really these appendages that listen to
누군가가 여기에있어 다음 드라이브는 정말 듣고이 부속된다
them so this is your inputs to in Iran and then it's got a single axon that
그 때문에이이란에 입력을하고 그것은 하나의 축삭을 가지고 그
comes out of a neuron that carries the output of the competition at this number
이 번호에 경쟁의 출력을 전달하는 신경 나오는
forms so usually usually have this neuron receives inputs if many of them
형태는 그래서 보통 일반적으로이 신경 세포는 그들 중 많은 경우 입력을 수신해야
online then this sell your own can choose to spike it sends an activation
온라인 다음이 판매 당신은 활성화를 전송 스파이크를 선택할 수 있습니다 자신의
potential down the axon and then this actually like that were just out to
축삭 아래로 잠재하고이 사실처럼 그냥 밖으로했다
connect to dendrites other neurons that are downstream so there are other
다운 스트림 다른 뉴런이 너무 다른가 수상 돌기에 연결
neurons here and their dendrites connected to the axons of these guys
이 사람의 축삭에 연결 여기에 신경과 수상 돌기
basically just neurons connected through these synapses between and we had these
기본적으로 그냥 사이의 이러한 시냅스를 통해 연결되어 있고 우리는이 있었다 뉴런
dendrites that Rd in particular on and this action on that actually carries the
특히 그 로드은에 수상 돌기과 그에이 작업은 실제로 운반
output on their own and so basically you can come up with a very crude model of a
자신의 등 기본적에 출력 당신은 매우 원유 모델을 가지고 올 수
neuron and it will look something like this we have so this is the cell body
우리가 신경과는 다음과 같이 보일 것입니다 그래서이 셀 몸
here on their own and just imagine an axon coming from a different neuron
여기에 자신에 단지 다른 신경 세포에서 나오는 축삭을 상상
someone at work and this neuron is connected to that Iran through this
직장에서 사람이 신경이를 통해이이란에 연결되어
synapse and every one of these synapses has a weight associated with it
시냅스 이러한 시냅스의 각 하나와 연관된 가중치를 갖는다
of how much this neuron likes that neuron basically and so actually carries
얼마나 많은이 신경 세포가 좋아하는 신경 세포는 기본적 그래서 실제로 수행하는 것이
this X it interacts in the synapse and they multiply and discrete model so you
이 X이는 시냅스에서 상호 작용하고 증식 및 이산 모델 당신 때문에
get W 00 flooding flowing to the summer and then that happens for many Iraqis
00 홍수가 여름에 흐르는 W 얻을 후 많은 이라크 인에 대한 일어나는
who have lots of
많이 가지고있는 사람
and puts up w times explosion and the cell body here it's just some offset by
및 시간의 폭발과는 좀 상쇄있어 여기 세포체 승두고
bias and then if an activation function is met here so it passes through an
바이어스 한 후이 통과되도록 활성화 기능이 여기에 충족되는 경우
activation function to actually complete the outfit of the sax on now in
활성화 기능은 실제로 지금의에 색소폰의 옷을 완료합니다
biological models historically people like to use the sigmoid nonlinearity to
생물학적 모델은 역사적으로 사람들에 S 상 비선형 성을 사용하려면
actually the reason for that is because you get a number between 0 and one and
는 0과 하나 사이의 수를 얻을 수 있기 때문에 실제로 그 이유는
you can interpret that as the rate at which this neuron inspiring for that
이 신경 세포가에 대한 영감을하는 속도로 그 해석 할 수 있습니다
particular input so it's a rate between zero and one that's going through the
그것은을 통해 일어나고 0과 1 사이의 비율이 그래서 특정 입력
activation function so if this neuron is seen something that likes in the neurons
이 신경 세포는 신경 세포에서 좋아하는 무언가를 볼 수있다, 그래서 만약 활성화 함수
that connected to it it will start to spike a lot and the rate is described by
연결된이 많이 스파이크 시작되고 속도에 의해 설명된다
F off the impact oK so that's the crude model of neuron if I wanted to implement
그게 내가 구현하고자한다면 신경 세포의 원유 모델은 그래서 충격 오프 F 확인
it would look something like this so and neuron function forward pass and receive
그것은이 너무과 신경 기능 전진 패스 같은 것을보고받을 것이다
some inputs this is a vector and reform of the cell body so just a lawyer some
일부 입력이 세포체 그래서 그냥 변호사 몇 가지의 벡터 개혁이다
and we put the firing rate as a sigmoid off the Somali some and return to firing
우리는 소말리아 일부를 S 자형으로 발사 속도를 넣고 발사로 돌아가
rate and then this can plug into different neurons right so you can
속도와 다음이 바로 그래서 당신이 할 수있는 다른 뉴런에 연결 할 수 있습니다
imagine you can actually see that this looks very similar to a linear
실제로이 선형과 매우 유사 보이는 것을 알 수 있습니다 상상
classifier radar for MIMO lehrer some here and we're passing through
일부 여기에 우리가 통과하는 MIMO의 레러에 대한 분류 레이더
nonlinearity so every single neuron in this model is really like a small your
비선형 그래서이 모델에 하나 하나 신경 세포는 작은처럼 정말 당신의
classifier but these authors plug into each other and they can work together to
분류 그러나이 저자는 서로 연결하고 그들에게 함께 작업 할 수 있습니다
do interesting things now 10 to make about neurons that they're very they're
그들은 매우 그들이있어있어 뉴런에 대해 지금 10 재미있는 일을
not like biological neurons biological neurons are super complex so if you go
생물학적 뉴런은 당신이 가고 그래서 만약 슈퍼 복잡한 생물학적 뉴런을 좋아하지
around then you start saying that neural networks work like brain people are
주위에 당신은 뇌의 사람들이 같은 신경 네트워크가 작동한다는 시작
starting to round people started firing at you and that's because there are
라운드 사람들에게 시작하는 당신을 발사하기 시작하고있다 때문이다
complex dynamical systems there are many different types of neurons they function
그들이 작동 뉴런의 많은 다른 종류가 복잡한 동적 시스템
differently these dendrites there they can perform lots of interesting
다르게이이 수상 돌기는 흥미를 많이 수행 할 수 있습니다
computation a good review article is in direct competition which I really
계산 좋은 리뷰 기사가 직접적인 경쟁이다 정말
enjoyed these synapses are complex dynamical systems they're not just a
이 시냅스는 복잡한 동적 시스템이다 그들은 그냥 아니에요 즐겼다
single weight and we're not really sure of the brain uses rate code to
우리는 뇌의 정말 확실하지 않은 단일 무게에 속도 코드를 사용
communicate so very crude mathematical model and don't put his analogy too much
그래서 매우 원유 수학적 모델을 전달하고 너무 많은 그의 비유를 넣지 마십시오
but it's good for a kind of like media articles
하지만 같은 미디어 제품의 종류에 좋은
so I suppose that's why this keeps coming up again and again as we
그래서 나는이 다시 올라오고 계속 그 이유는 우리로 다시 겠
explained that this works like a brain but I'm not going to go too deep into
설명이 뇌처럼 작동하지만 난 너무 깊이에 갈 아니에요
this to go back to a question that was asked for there's an entire set of
의 전체 세트 거기에이 질문 한 질문으로 돌아갑니다
nonlinearities that we can choose from so historically signal has been used
우리가 역사적으로 신호를 선택할 수 있습니다 비선형가 사용되었습니다
quite a bit and we're going to go into much more detail over what these
꽤는 그리고 우리는 무엇을이 이상 더 많은 세부 사항으로 갈거야
nonlinearities are what are their trades tradeoffs and why you might want to use
비선형는 거래의 장단점이 무엇이며 왜 사용 할 수 있습니다
one or the other but for now just like a flash to mention that there are many to
하나 또는 다른하지만​​ 플래시가 많은이 있다는 것을 언급하는 것처럼 지금은
choose from
에서 선택
historically people use to 10 H as of 2012 really became quite popular
정말 아주 인기가 2012 년으로 역사적으로 사람들은 H (10)에 사용
it makes your networks quite a bit faster so right now if you want a
당신이 원하는 경우 더 빨리 그래서 지금 당신의 네트워크를 꽤한다
default choice for nonlinearity
비선형의 기본 선택
relew that's the current default recommendation and then there's a few
즉 현재의 디폴트 추천 그리고 relew 다음 몇 가지있다
activation functions here and so are proposed a few years ago I max out is
여기 이렇게 활성화 기능은 내가 밖으로는 최대 몇 년 전 제안
interesting and very recently you lou and so you can come up with different
재미 있고 아주 최근에 루 그래서 당신은 다른 가지고 올 수
activation functions and you can describe I these might work better or
활성화 기능과 내가이 더 잘 작동 할 수 설명 할 수 있습니다 또는
not and so this is an active area of research is trying to go up by the
그래서이 연구의 활성 영역은에 의해 이동을 시도되지 않으며
activation functions that perform there had better properties in one way or
이 수행 활성화 기능을 하나의 방법으로 더 좋은 특성을 가지고 또는
another we're going to go into this much more details as soon in class but for
또 다른 우리는 클래스에 있지만뿐만 곧 더 많은 세부 사항으로 갈거야
now we have these morons we have a choice of activation function and then
이제 우리는 활성화 함수의 선택의 여지가 이러한 바보가
we runs these neurons into neural networks right so we just connect them
우리는 바로 그래서 우리는 단지 그들을 연결하는 신경 네트워크에 이러한 신경 세포를 실행
together so they can talk to each other and so here is an example of a what to
함께 그들이 그렇게 여기에 서로 통신 할 수 있도록하는 것은 무엇의 예입니다
learn or relearn rowlett when you want to count the number of layers and their
배우 또는 레이어와의 수를 계산하려면 rowlett을 재 학습 자신의
neural net you count the number of players that happened waits to hear the
신경망 당신은 듣고 대기 일어난 선수의 수를 계산
input layer does not count as a later cuz there's no reason Iran's largest
이유이란 최대가 없습니다 사촌 입력 층은 나중에로 계산하지 않습니다
single values they don't actually do any computation so we have two players here
우리는 여기에 두 선수가되도록 하나의 값은 실제로 어떤 계산을하지 않는다
that that have weights to learn it and we call these layers fully connected
무게가 그 그게 배우는 우리는 완전히 연결이 레이어를 호출
layers and so that I shown you that a single neuron computer this little
레이어와 내가 당신 단일 신경 세포 시스템이 작은 그런를 표시하는 것이
weight at some and ambassador nonlinearity in a neural network the
신경 네트워크의 일부 대사 비선형의 중량
reason we arrange these into layers is because Iranian them into layers allows
레이어로이란은 수 있기 때문에 우리가 층으로 이들을 배치 이유는
us to the competition much more efficiently so instead of having an
경쟁에 우리를 훨씬 더 효율적 그래서 대신의를 갖는
amorphous blob of neurons and every one of them has to be computed independently
비정질 뉴런의 얼룩과 그들 모두 독립적으로 계산되어야한다
having them in layers allows us to use vectorized operations and so we can
레이어를 갖는 벡터화 작업을 사용하는 우리를 허용하고 그래서 우리는 할 수 있습니다
compute an entire set of
의 전체 세트를 계산할
neurons in a single hidden layer as just a single times amateurs multiply and
아마추어 곱 단지 하나의 배 하나의 숨겨진 계층의 뉴런과
that's why we arrange them in these layers where Iran since I deliver and
그것이 우리가이 층을 배치 이유 곳이란 내가 제공 이후 및
evaluate it completely in peril and they all say the same thing but it's a
완전히 위험 그것을 평가 모두 동일한 것을 말하지만, 이것은 A의
computational trick to arrange them in leaders this is a three-layer neural net
계산 트릭이는 3 층 신경망 인 지도자로 정렬하기
and this is how you would compute it just a bunch of major multiplies
이것은 당신이 주요 곱셈의 단지 무리를 계산하는 방법을이다
followed by another activation followed by activation function as well now I'd
지금뿐만 아니라 활성 기능에 의해 나는 것 다음에 다른 활성화 한 다음
like to show you a demo of how these neural networks work so this is just
그래서 이것은 그냥 당신이 신경 네트워크가 작동하는 방법의 데모를 보여 드리고자
grabbed a model shoot you in a bit but basically this is an example of a
모델은 약간 당신을 촬영하지만, 기본적으로 이것은의 예입니다 잡고는
two-layer neural network classifying AP doing a binary classification task two
두 층은 신경망 AP 이진 분류 업무 개의 하 분류
closest red and green and so if these points in two dimensions and I'm drawing
가장 가까운 빨간색과 녹색 등 두 가지 차원에서 이러한 점은 내가 그리는거야 경우
the decision boundaries by the neural network and see what you can see is when
신경망에 의해 결정 경계와는 당신이 볼 수있는 것은 때입니다 참조
I train a neural network on this data the more hidden neurons I have in my
나는이 데이터를 내가에있는 더 많은 숨겨진 뉴런 신경 네트워크를 양성 내
head in later the more wiggle your electric cars right the more can compute
당신의 전기 자동차가 오른쪽으로 더 계산할 수 나중에 더 호기심 머리
crazy functions and just show you also a regularization strength so this is the
미친 기능은 당신이 또한 정규화 강도 그래서이는 것을 보여
regularization of how much you penalize large W you can see that when you insist
당신 W 큰 불이익을 어느 정도의 정규화 당신이 주장 할 때 볼 수 있습니다
that your WR very small you end up with a very smooth functions so they don't
그렇지 않은 귀하의 WR 당신은 매우 부드러운 기능을 아주 작은 끝낼 것을
have as much variance so these neural networks there's not as much wriggle
많은 몸부림이 아니라 이러한 신경망 있도록 많은 차이가
that they can give you and then you decrease the regularization these know
그들은 당신을 제공 할 수 있습니다 그리고 당신은이 알고있는 정규화를 감소하는 것이
that we can do more and more complex tasks so they can kind of get in and get
그들이 종류의에서 얻을 얻을 수 있도록 우리는 점점 더 복잡한 작업을 할 수있는
these laws squeezed out points to cover them in the training data so let me show
훈련 데이터를 포함하는 점을 압착이 법은 그렇게 나에게 쇼를 보자
you what this looks like
당신이 어떻게 생겼는지
during training
훈련 도중
so there's some stuff to explain here let me first actually you can play with
그래서 여기에 설명 첫번째 실제로 당신이 놀 수있는 날 수 있도록하기 위해 몇 가지 물건이있다
this because it's all in javascript
이는 자바 스크립트 전부 때문에
alright so we're doing here as we have six neurons and this is a binary
확실히 우리가 여섯 뉴런을 가지고 우리는 여기에서하고있는이 이진입니다
classification there said with circle data and so we have a little cluster of
분류가 원 데이터와 상기 그래서 우리의 작은 클러스터가
green dot separated by red dots and work training a neural network to classify
분류 신경망을 훈련 빨간색 점과 직장으로 구분 녹색 점
this dataset so if I restart the neural network it's just started off with the
내가 신경 네트워크를 다시 시작하면 그것이 바로 진형 그래서이 데이터 집합
random W and that it converges the decision boundary to actually classified
W 무작위 실제로 분류하는 결정 경계 수렴
the data showing on the right which is the cool part is one interpretation of
시원한 부분 오른쪽에 표시 데이터 중 하나 해석
the neural network here is what I'm taking that's great to hear and I'm
여기에 신경 네트워크는 내가 그 데려 갈거야 것은 듣기 좋은 그리고 난입니다
showing how this space gets worked by the neural network so you can interpret
이 공간은 신경 네트워크에 의해 작동되는 방법을 보여주는 것은 그래서 당신은 해석 할 수 있습니다
what the neural network is doing is it's using its hidden layer to transport your
무엇 신경 네트워크가하고있는 것은 수송 숨겨진 층을 사용하고 당신의
input data in such a way that the second hidden layer can come in with a linear
제 은닉층 선형으로 올 수있는 방식으로 입력 데이터
classifier and classify your data so here you see that the neural network
분류 및 신경망이 볼 여기에 귀하의 데이터를 분류
arranges your space it works it such that the second layer which is really a
그것을 정상적으로 작동 공간이 배치되도록 실제로, 상기 제 2 층
linear classifier on top of the first layer is can put a plane through it okay
제 1 층의 상단에 선형 분류는 괜찮 통해 비행기를 넣을 수있다
so it's working the space so that you can put the plane through it and
당신이 그것을 통해 비행기를 넣어 수 있도록 그래서 공간을 일하고
separate out the points so let's look at this again so you can really see what
포인트가 그래서 당신은 정말 볼 수 있도록 이제 다시 살펴 보자 분리 해 무엇을
happens gets worked for that you can leave early classify the data this is
당신이이 데이터를 분류 일찍 떠날 수있는 근무되는 일이 발생
something that people sometimes also referred to as current trek it's
사람들은 때때로 그것의 현재 여행이라 뭔가
changing your data representation to a space where two linearly separable ok
공간에 데이터 표현을 변경하는 경우 두 개의 선형 분리 확인
now here's a question if we'd like to separate the right now we have six
지금 여기에 우리가 지금 우리가 육이 권리를 분리하려는 경우 질문입니다
neurons here and the intermediate layer and it allows us to separate out these
여기 뉴런과 중간층과 우리가 이러한 분리를 허용
things so you can see actually those six neurons roughly you can see these lines
당신이 실제로 그 여섯 신경 세포를 볼 수 있도록 일들이 대략 이러한 라인을 볼 수 있습니다
here like they're kind of like these functions of one of these neurons so
그들은 종류의 때문에 이러한 뉴런의 하나의 이러한 기능 같아 여기처럼
here's a question for you what is the minimum number of neurons for which this
여기에 신경 세포의 최소 숫자가 무엇인지에 대한 질문입니다 어떤이에 대한
dataset is separable with a neural network like if I want to know that work
내가 그 일을 알고 싶다면 데이터 세트는 신경 네트워크 등으로 분리 가능
to correctly classify this as a minimum
제대로 최소한이 분류하는
so into it with the way this work is 34 so what happens with or is there is one
그래서에 방법이 작업은 34 그렇게하여 발생하거나 무슨 일이있다
around here that went from this way to that way this way to that way this way
여기에 주변이 그런 식으로이 방법을 그런 식으로이 방법에서이 방법을 갔다
to that way there's more neurons that are cutting up this plane and then
그 방법으로 다음 더이 비행기를 절단하는 뉴런하고있다
there's an additional layer that's a weighted sum so in fact the lowest
가중 합계의 추가 계층이있다 가장 낮은 사실 때문에
number here what would be three which would work so with three neurons ok so
수는 여기에 무엇을 확인 세 개의 신경 세포로 그렇게 일하는 것이 세 것
one plane second plane airplane so three linear functions within the linearity
하나의 평면 제 2 평면 비행기 선형성 내에서 세 개의 선형 함수
and then you can basically with three lines you can carve out the space so
다음은 기본적으로 세 가지 라인으로 그렇게 공간을 개척 할 수 있습니다
that the second layer can just combined them when their numbers are 102
그 수는 102 인 경우 제 2 층은 단지 그들 결합 수
certainly donate to this will break because two lines are not enough I
두 줄이 충분 I하지 않기 때문에 확실히 깰 것이에 기부
suppose this work something very good here so with to basically it will find
기본적으로는 찾을 수와 그래서 여기에 아주 좋은이 작업 뭔가를 가정
the optimum way of just using these two lines they're kind of creating this
단지 그들이 종류의이 만드는이 두 줄을 사용하는 최적의 방법
tunnel and that the best you can do
터널과 최고의 것을 당신은 할 수있다
I think if I was using rather I think there would be much surrealism and I
나는 오히려 사용하는 경우 나는 많은 초현실주의 내가있을 것이라고 생각 생각
think you'd see sharp boundaries yeah you can do for now let's do it because
당신이 날카로운 경계를 볼 수있을 거라고 생각 당신이 지금 할 수있는 네의이 있기 때문에 그것을 할 수 있습니다
some of these parts
이러한 부품의 일부
there's more than one of those revenues are active and so you end up with there
그 수익의 둘 이상의 활성 그래서 당신이와 끝까지있다
are really three lines I think like 123 but then in some of the corners to revel
내가 123처럼 생각 정말 세 줄하지만 다음에에게 모서리 중 일부는 푹 빠졌하기
in your eyes are active and so these weights will have its kind of funky you
눈에 활성 등이 가중치는 펑키의 종류있을 것이다 당신
have to think about it but ok so let's look at say twenty here so change to 20
그것에 대해 생각해야하지만, 확인 그러니에서 그렇게 20로 변경 여기 스무 말을 살펴 보자
so we have lots of space there and let's look at different assets like a spiral
그래서 우리는이 공간을 많이 가지고의 나선형처럼 다른 자산을 살펴 보자
you can see how this thing just as I'm doing this update will just go in there
당신은 그냥 거기에 가서이 업데이트를하고 있어요 것처럼 어떻게이 일을 볼 수 있습니다
and figure that out very simple data that is not my own circle and then ran
내 자신의 원없는 매우 간단한 데이터를 알아낼 후 실행
him down so you could kind of goes in there and it's like covers up the green
그 아래는 그래서 당신은 가지가 간다 수 있고 녹색을 커버처럼입니다
lawns and the red ones and yeah and with fewer say like I'm going to break this
잔디와 붉은 색과 그래 내가이 깰거야처럼 적은 수의 말과
now I'm not going to go with five yes this will start working worse and worse
지금은 오 갈 않을거야 그래이 더 악화 작업을 시작합니다
because you don't have enough capacity to separate out this data so you can
당신은 당신이 할 수 있도록이 데이터를 분리 할 수​​있는 충분한 능력이 없기 때문에
play with this in your free time and so as a summary
당신의 자유 시간 및 요약도록이 놀이
we arrange these neurons and neural networks into political heirs
우리는 정치적 후계자로 이러한 신경 세포와 신경 네트워크를 배치
look at that crop and how this gets changing competition graphs and they're
그 작물을보고이 경쟁 그래프를 변경 얻을 방법을 그들이있어
not really neural and as you'll see soon the bigger the better and we'll go into
정말 신경과 곧 볼 수와 같은 더 큰 더 나은 우리는에 갈거야
that a lot I want to take questions before I am just sorry questions we have
나는 우리가 그냥 미안 질문을 생각하기 전에 내가 원하는 많은 질문을하는 것을
two more minutes
두 분 이상
yes thank you
네 감사합니다
so is it always better to have more neurons and neural network the answer to
그래서 더 신경과 신경 네트워크 대답에이 항상 더 낫다
that is yes more is always better it's usually competition constraint so more
그 네 더 그렇게 더 일반적으로 경쟁 제한의 항상 더 나은입니다
always work better but then you have to be careful to regularize it properly so
항상 잘 작동하지만 당신은 조심해야하므로 제대로 정례화하기
the correct way to constrain you're not worked over put your data is not by
당신이 당신의 데이터를 넣어 이상 일하지 않는 제한 할 수있는 올바른 방법으로하지 않습니다
making the network smaller the correct way to do it is to increase the
작은 네트워크를 할 수있는 올바른 방법을 만드는 것은 증가하는 것입니다
regularization so you always want to use as larger network as you want but then
정규화 당신은 항상 당신이 원하는대로 큰 네트워크로 사용할 그래서하지만
you have to make sure to properly regulate rise it but most of the time
당신은 대부분의 시간을 적절하게 상승 조절할 확인해야하지만,
because competition reasons why I don't have time to wait forever to train our
나는 훈련을 영원히 기다릴 시간이없는 이유는 경쟁의 이유 때문에 우리
networks use smaller ones for practical reasons question arises equally
실제적인 이유 질문은 동일하게 발생에 대한 네트워크는 작은 것을 사용
usually you do as a simplification you yeah most of the often when you see
일반적으로 당신은 당신이 좋아 당신이 대부분을 자주 볼 단순화과 같이
networks trained in practice they will be regularized the same way throughout
실제로 훈련 네트워크들은 동일한 방법 전반을 정규화한다
but you don't have to necessarily
하지만 당신은 반드시 필요 없어요
is anybody using secondary option in optimizing networks there is value
값이 누구 최적화 네트워크에 보조 옵션을 사용
sometimes when your data sets are small you can use things like lbs which I
데이터 세트가 작은 경우 때때로 당신은 파운드 같은 것들을 사용할 수있는 I
don't go into too much and it's the second order method but usually the data
너무 들어가서 보통 2 차 방법하지만 데이터의하지
sets are really large and that's when I'll get you it doesn't work very well
세트는 정말 크고, 그것이 내가 당신을 얻을 것이다 때 매우 잘 작동하지 않습니다이다
so you when you millions of the up with you can't do lbs for ya and LBJ is not
그래서 당신은 당신과 함께 최대의 당신 수백만 나중에에 대한 파운드를 할 수없는 경우와 LBJ는 아니다
very good with many batch you always have to fall back by default
많은 배치 매우 좋은 당신은 항상 기본적으로 후퇴해야
like how do you allocate not a good answer for that unfortunately so you
같은 방법 당신 때문에 불행하게도 그에 대한 좋은 대답을하지 할당 할
want a depth is good but maybe after like ten layers may be a simple data
깊이가 양호하지만 어쩌면 같은 후 열 층은 간단한 데이터 일 수있다 싶어
said it's not really adding too much in one minute so I can still take some
말했다 정말 내가 여전히 걸릴 수 있습니다 1 분 너무 많이 추가 아니에요
questions you have a question for the tradeoff between where do I allocate my
질문은 내가 할당 않는 곳 사이의 트레이드 오프에 대한 질문이 내
capacity to I want us to be deeper or do I want it to be wider not a very good
나는 우리가 깊은되고 싶어하거나 수행에 용량 나는 그것이 매우 좋은 넓은지지 않습니다 싶어
answer to that yes usually especially with images we find that more layers are
일반적으로, 특히 이미지와 함께 우리는 더 많은 층이 발견이 yes로 응답
critical but sometimes when you have simple tastes like to do you are some
중요하지만 때로는 당신이있을 때 간단한 취향은 몇 가지 작업을 수행하려면
other things like depth is not as critical and so it's kind of slightly
깊이와 같은 다른 것들하지 중요하고 그래서 약간 종류의
data dependent
종속 데이터
different for different layers that health usually it's not done usually
건강이 보통 일반적으로하지있어 다른 레이어에 대해 서로 다른
just gonna pick one and go with it that's for example will also see the
그냥 거 하나를 선택하고 또한 표시됩니다 예를 들어있어 그것으로 이동
most of them are changes with others and so you just use that throughout and
그들 중 대부분은 다른 사람과 변경하고 그래서 당신은 단지 전체에 그것을 사용하고
there's no real benefit to to switch them around people don't play with that
사람들이 그와 함께 연주하지 않는 주위를 전환 할 수있는 실제 혜택은 없습니다
too much on principle you there's nothing preventing you are so it is 420
원칙에 너무 많은 당신이 그래서 420입니다 있습니다 방지 아무것도 없다
so we're going to end here but we'll see a lot more neural networks so a lot of
그래서 우리는 여기서 끝나지거야하지만 우리는 많은 있도록 더 많은 신경 네트워크를 볼 수 있습니다
these questions will go through them
이러한 질문은 그들을 통해 이동합니다